<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e01-Pilot</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e01-pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e01-pilot/</guid>
      <description>s01e01-Pilot All right, Jim. Your quarterlies look very good. - How are things at the library? - I told you. I couldn&#39;t close it. So you&#39;ve come to the master for guidance? Is this what you&#39;re saying, grasshopper? Actually, you called me in here, but, yeah. All right. Well, let me show you how it&#39;s done. I&#39;d like to speak to your office manager, please. Yes, hello. This is Michael Scott.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e02-Diversity Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e02-diversity-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e02-diversity-day/</guid>
      <description>s01e02-Diversity Day Hiya. Can I help you out here? - I&#39;m all set, thanks. - Gotcha. Good. I&#39;d go with the rose. That&#39;s a good idea. Today is diversity day and someone&#39;s going to come in and talk to us about diversity. It&#39;s something that I&#39;ve been pushing, that I&#39;ve been wanting to push, for a long time and Corporate mandated it. And I never actually talked to Corporate about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e03-Health Care</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e03-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e03-health-care/</guid>
      <description>s01e03-Health Care Pam. Pamela. Pam-elama-ding-dong. - Making copies. - I&#39;m not making any copies. Let&#39;s go. Messages. Stat. Lots to do, lots to do. Information superhighway. - Nothing new. - Lay them on moi. What? - There&#39;s nothing new. - That&#39;s not what you said earlier. Do you want me to repeat the messages that I gave you before for the The most sacred thing I do is care and provide for my workers, my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e04-The Alliance</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e04-the-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e04-the-alliance/</guid>
      <description>s01e04-The Alliance - Michael? - Oh, God. Dwight, come on - About the downsizing - There is none. But if there were, I&#39;d be protected as assistant regional manager? - Assistant to the regional manager. - So I needn&#39;t worry? Look, I talked to Corporate about protecting sales staff. They couldn&#39;t guarantee it if we downsize. - But we&#39;re not downsizing, so - Bottom line. Do I need to be worried?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e05-Basketball</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e05-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e05-basketball/</guid>
      <description>s01e05-Basketball Hey. You ready? All right. Secret sign. Hey, Ryan. Very good. Excellent. Excellent. Michael. Today at lunchtime we&#39;re going to be playing the warehouse staff at a friendly little game of basketball. My idea. I noticed they&#39;d put up a couple of hoops and I play basketball every weekend so I thought, &amp;quot;This might be kinda fun. &amp;quot; And I started messing around and Im sinking a few, you know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s01e06-Hot Girl</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e06-hot-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s01e06-hot-girl/</guid>
      <description>s01e06-Hot Girl Are you listening to me? - Affirmative. What did I just say? You just said Let me check my notes. You just said Alan and I have created an incentive program How is Alan? Tell Alan that the Mets suck. OK? From me, big time. Go Pirates! I&#39;m not going to do that. We&#39;ve created an incentive program to increase sales. You can reward your top seller with a prize worth up to $1,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e01-The Dundies</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e01-the-dundies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e01-the-dundies/</guid>
      <description>s02e01-The Dundies MICHAEL: Tonight is the Dundies, the annual employee awards night here at Dunder Mifflin. And this is everybody&#39;s favorite day. Everybody looks forward to it, because, you know, a lot of the people here don&#39;t get trophies very often, like Meredith or Kevin. I mean, who&#39;s gonna give Kevin an award? Dunkin&#39; Donuts? Plus, bonus, it&#39;s really, really funny. So I You know, an employee will go home and he&#39;ll tell his neighbor, &amp;quot;Hey, did you get an award?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e02-Sexual Harassment</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e02-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e02-sexual-harassment/</guid>
      <description>s02e02-Sexual Harassment (PHONE RINGING) (CLEARING THROAT) Hey, what&#39;s up? Hey. Any e-mails today? I don&#39;t think so. No? Check your spam folder. There it is. What? &amp;quot;Fifty signs your priest might be Michael Jackson. &amp;quot; Well done. Kidding. Topical. MICHAEL: I am &amp;quot;King of Forwards. &amp;quot; It&#39;s how I like to do business. Everybody joking around. We&#39;re like Friends. I am Chandler and Joey. And Pam is Rachel. And Dwight is Kramer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e03-Office Olympics</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e03-office-olympics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e03-office-olympics/</guid>
      <description>s02e03-Office Olympics MICHAEL: I&#39;m an early bird and I&#39;m a night owl. So I&#39;m wise and I have worms. (KNOCKING ON DOOR) MICHAEL: Oh, breakfast. I got your sausage, egg and cheese biscuit. Yummy, yummy, thank you, Ryan. What was the thing you needed me to come in early for? Um The sausage, egg and cheese biscuit. But, thank you. And why don&#39;t you just take a couple hours. Office is yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e04-The Fire</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e04-the-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e04-the-fire/</guid>
      <description>s02e04-The Fire Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam. Sure, can I ask who&#39;s calling? Just a second. (TELEPHONE RINGING) Jim Halpert. What? How did you get this number? Stalker. Katy and Jim met in the office. PAM: And now, I guess they&#39;re, like, going out or dating or something. And I don&#39;t know, you know. They&#39;re just She calls him, and they You know. I&#39;m sorry, I feel like I&#39;m talking really loud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e05-Halloween</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e05-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e05-halloween/</guid>
      <description>s02e05-Halloween Happy Halloween, everyone! Oh, that&#39;s great. Hey. Happy Halloween. Jan called. (SIGHS) Okay. I know why she&#39;s calling. It&#39;s the end of the month, and I was supposed to let somebody go by the end of the month. (SIGHS) And somehow I&#39;m supposed to put on a costume and smile. (TELEPHONE RINGING) Okay. SHERRY: Jan Levinson&#39;s office. Hey, Sherry, Michael Scott returning. Oh, she&#39;s in a meeting. She just wanted the name of the employee you let go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e06-The Fight</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e06-the-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e06-the-fight/</guid>
      <description>s02e06-The Fight Where is my desk? That is weird. This is not funny. This is totally unprofessional. Okay, well, you&#39;re the one who lost the desk. I didn&#39;t lose my desk. Hey, calm down. Where was the last place you saw it? Okay, who moved my desk? JIM: I think you should retrace your steps. Okay, I am going to tell Michael and this entire office will be punished. Colder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e07-The Client</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e07-the-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e07-the-client/</guid>
      <description>s02e07-The Client Hey, have they left for the big meeting yet? I got Michael&#39;s lucky tie. No, they&#39;re in the conference room. Okay. Wait. Are those Michael&#39;s Levi&#39;s? Yeah. Who dry-cleans jeans? PAM: Michael and his jeans. He gets in them, and I&#39;m not exactly sure what happens, but I can tell you he loves the way he looks in those jeans. I know that&#39;s why he started Casual Fridays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e08-Performance Review</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e08-performance-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e08-performance-review/</guid>
      <description>s02e08-Performance Review You should get one of these. No, thank you. Do you even know what this is? It is a fitness orb and it has completely changed my life. Forget everything you thought you knew about ab workouts. Done. This ab workout is specifically designed to strengthen your core. Sorry. It&#39;s all right. Numerous health benefits, strengthens your back, better performance in sports, more enjoyable sex. You&#39;re not having sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e09-E-Mail Surveillance</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e09-e-mail-surveillance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e09-e-mail-surveillance/</guid>
      <description>s02e09-E-Mail Surveillance It is Friday morning and it is another beautiful day in Scranton, Pennsylvania. (GASPS) Oh, my God! Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up. We have a serious problem here. All right everybody, lock the doors, turn off the lights. Pretend you&#39;re not here. Are we in danger? There&#39;s no time to think about it, this is real. Just Everybody (KNOCKING ON DOOR) KEVIN: Michael, should I call the What?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e10-Christmas Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e10-christmas-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e10-christmas-party/</guid>
      <description>s02e10-Christmas Party DWIGHT: Go. Get the door. MICHAEL: Here we are. DWIGHT: Go. Push. Oh, God. DWIGHT: Push. No, no, no. Turn it around. Really shove it. You&#39;ll break it. Shove it through. Break it! MICHAEL: You shove it. Shove it back. MICHAEL: Here we go. Don&#39;t break the branches, Dwight. All right. I got a splinter. Well, suck it up. We all have problems. (DWIGHT PANTING) Hey, everybody. Look what we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e11-Booze Cruise</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e11-booze-cruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e11-booze-cruise/</guid>
      <description>s02e11-Booze Cruise Hey. Hello. Jim! What&#39;s up, buddy? This is not funny. Why is my stuff in here? JIM: That&#39;s weird. A dollar for a stapler, that&#39;s pretty good. Yeah, well, I&#39;m not paying for my own stuff, okay? I know you did this, &#39;cause you&#39;re friends with the vending machine guy. Who, Steve? Yeah, Steve. Whatever his name is. What do I want? What do I want? (EXCLAIMS) It&#39;s a pencil cup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e12-The Injury</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e12-the-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e12-the-injury/</guid>
      <description>s02e12-The Injury Well, Lords of the Ring trilogy, if you see it back to back, Yeah. it&#39;s really long, but it&#39;s good. Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam. Pam, it&#39;s Michael. Help me. I need help right now! Michael, what&#39;s wrong? I&#39;m hurt. I have hurt myself. (GROANING) Oh, my God! Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait! Oh, this is not looking good, Pam. Michael, do you need me to call an ambulance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e13-The Secret</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e13-the-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e13-the-secret/</guid>
      <description>s02e13-The Secret Nothing much, what&#39;s up with you? I cannot believe I fell for that. Oh, my gosh! What? What? Where&#39;s the funny? Give it to me. Is it me or does it smell like updog in here? What&#39;s &amp;quot;updog&amp;quot;? Nothing much, what&#39;s up with you? Oh, wow. I walked right into that. Oh, that&#39;s brilliant. Hey, Stanley, is that jacket made of updog? I&#39;m on the phone. (STANLEY CHATTERING) What flavor coffee is that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e14-The Carpet</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e14-the-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e14-the-carpet/</guid>
      <description>s02e14-The Carpet What? Oh, nothing. Pam&#39;s on vacation and she gets back tomorrow, so it&#39;ll be nice to see her. It&#39;ll be nice. And she set a date for the wedding with Roy. June. Summer. So, that&#39;ll be nice. And that&#39;s that. (PHONE RINGING) What? Oh, nothing. Jim&#39;s been looking at me, kind of, a lot all week. I would be creeped out by it, but it&#39;s nothing compared to the way Michael looks at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e15-Boys &amp; Girls</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e15-boys-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e15-boys-girls/</guid>
      <description>s02e15-Boys &amp;amp; Girls So, I&#39;m happy to be here. It&#39;s very nice to see all of you. You&#39;re all looking well. Today is a &amp;quot;women in the workplace&amp;quot; thing. Jan&#39;s coming in from Corporate to talk to all the women about I don&#39;t really know what. But Michael&#39;s not allowed in. She said that about five times. Women today, though we have the same options as men, we often face a very different set of obstacles (KNOCKING ON DOOR) In getting there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e16-Valentine&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e16-valentines-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e16-valentines-day/</guid>
      <description>s02e16-Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day (PHONE RINGING) I really like Valentine&#39;s Day in this office. It&#39;s kind of like grade school. Everybody gives out little presents and stuff. Like, last year, Jim gave me this card with Dwight&#39;s head on it. It was horrifying and funny and (DOOR OPENS) Phyllis. MAN: You could just sign here. PAM: Roy and I are saving for the wedding. So I made him promise not to get me anything too big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e17-Dwight&#39;s Speech</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e17-dwights-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e17-dwights-speech/</guid>
      <description>s02e17-Dwight&amp;rsquo;s Speech Let&#39;s think this through. If we ask corporate for that, then They are either gonna say yes or no. MICHAEL: Could go either way. We don&#39;t know what they are going to say. Think it through! We have to think it through! Because, if they say no Can we not? No Yes, we have to. You know why? &#39;Cause I don&#39;t like to be cooped up in that office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e18-Take Your Daughter to Work Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e18-take-your-daughter-to-work-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e18-take-your-daughter-to-work-day/</guid>
      <description>s02e18-Take Your Daughter to Work Day PAM: I am actually looking forward to &amp;quot;Take Your Daughter to Work Day. &amp;quot; I am not great with kids, but I wanna get better because I&#39;m getting married. So I put out a bunch of extra candy on my desk so the kids will come talk to me. Like the witch in Hansel and Gretel. Bribery. Nice. Oh, I have more. Name&#39;s Pam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e19-Michael&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e19-michaels-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e19-michaels-birthday/</guid>
      <description>s02e19-Michael&amp;rsquo;s Birthday So, Phil recruited me to sell these cards, and now I am recruiting you. Who is this guy again? Don&#39;t worry about Phil. He drives a Corvette. He&#39;s doing just fine. Okay. Calling cards are the wave of the future. These things sell themselves. Who uses calling cards anymore? You know what? That&#39;s a nice attitude, Ryan. I&#39;m just helping you invest in your future, my friend. It sounds like a get-rich-quick scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e20-Drug Testing</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e20-drug-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e20-drug-testing/</guid>
      <description>s02e20-Drug Testing DWIGHT: Kevin Malone, you&#39;re next. Spit that out. Spit. Okay, come on. Let&#39;s go. You look cute today, Dwight. Thanks, girl. So, yesterday Dwight found half a joint in the parking lot, which is unfortunate, because, as it turns out, Dwight finding drugs is more dangerous than most people using drugs. Let&#39;s go over some of these symptoms of marijuana use, shall we? You tell me who this sounds like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e21-Conflict Resolution</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e21-conflict-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e21-conflict-resolution/</guid>
      <description>s02e21-Conflict Resolution So have you found a band yet for your wedding? No. &#39;Cause I&#39;m in a band. We really rock. Yeah. I mean, it&#39;s inevitable. I definitely overhear some wedding preparation, but I&#39;m fine with it. She hears me arranging my social life. And we both have to hear Dwight order deer urine over the Internet. So it evens out. Oh, I got the Save-the-Date. Yeah? Yeah. Pretty stationery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s02e22-Casino Night</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e22-casino-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s02e22-casino-night/</guid>
      <description>s02e22-Casino Night MICHAEL: Tonight the Scranton Business Park is having Casino Night and we are converting our warehouse into a full-blown gambling hall. And I know it&#39;s illegal in Pennsylvania, but it&#39;s for charity. And I consider myself a great philanderer. It&#39;s just It&#39;s nice to know, at the end of the day, I can look in the mirror and say, &amp;quot;Michael, because of you, some little kid in the Congo &amp;quot;has a belly full of rice this evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e01-Gay Witch Hunt</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e01-gay-witch-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e01-gay-witch-hunt/</guid>
      <description>s03e01-Gay Witch Hunt Yeah, I&#39;m not a temp anymore. I got Jim&#39;s old job, which means at my 10-year high school reunion, it will not say, &amp;quot;Ryan Howard is a temp. &amp;quot; It will say, &amp;quot;Ryan Howard is a junior sales associate &amp;quot;at a mid-range paper supply firm. &amp;quot; That&#39;ll show them. You have no idea how long I&#39;ve wanted to do that. Me, too. I think we&#39;re just drunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e02-The Convention</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e02-the-convention/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e02-the-convention/</guid>
      <description>s03e02-The Convention Pam? Yeah? Did you see Oprah yesterday? No, I didn&#39;t. I I&#39;m going to be a father. What was Oprah about? Angelina Jolie was on. And she adopted a baby from Asia, and she said that it changed her life, and that really inspired me. So I want you to look into see how much a little Chinese baby would cost. That&#39;s a really big decision. I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e03-The Coup</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e03-the-coup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e03-the-coup/</guid>
      <description>s03e03-The Coup I&#39;m hungry. Movie Monday! The only cure I know for the Monday blues is Varsity Blues. Let&#39;s go! Let&#39;s go, let&#39;s go, let&#39;s go! Take a seat down there. Second from the end. All right. Everybody here? Yes! Popcorn, anyone? Yes, please! Thank you. Anyone else? No. Movie Monday started with training videos. But we went through those pretty fast. Then we watched a medical video. Since then, it&#39;s been half-hour installments of various movies, with the exception of an episode of Entourage, which Michael made us watch six times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e04-Grief Counseling</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e04-grief-counseling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e04-grief-counseling/</guid>
      <description>s03e04-Grief Counseling Hey, Ryan, can I get you a pencil from the warehouse? Oh, no, thanks. I&#39;m good. Well, it&#39;s okay. I&#39;m going down. Yeah. Absolutely. All right, I&#39;ll be right back. Awesome. Thank you. You&#39;re welcome. Michael, could you get me a pen from down in the warehouse? Don&#39;t mind if I do. See you in a minute. Okay! There you go, fresh from the warehouse. Hey, Michael, would you get me some coffee from the warehouse?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e05-Initiation</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e05-initiation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e05-initiation/</guid>
      <description>s03e05-Initiation Brain teaser. I have two coins, totaling 15 cents. One of them is not a nickel. What are they? A dime and a nickel. No. I said one of them is not a nickel. But the other one is. I&#39;ve heard that before. Okay. A man and his son get into a car accident. They are rushed to the hospital. The doctor says, &amp;quot;There is no way I can operate on this boy &amp;quot; &amp;quot;Because he&#39;s my son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e06-Diwali</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e06-diwali/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e06-diwali/</guid>
      <description>s03e06-Diwali There you go. Nice dress, Ryan. It&#39;s not a dress, it&#39;s a kurta. Okay. Tonight, one of our most ethnic co-workers, Kelly, has invited us all to a Diwali celebration put on by her community. What is Diwali, you may ask? Well, to have Kelly explain it, &amp;quot;It&#39;s I have It&#39;s so super fun and it&#39;s gonna be great. &amp;quot; A lot of gods with unpronounceable names. Twenty minutes later you find out that it&#39;s essentially a Hindu Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e07-Branch Closing</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e07-branch-closing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e07-branch-closing/</guid>
      <description>s03e07-Branch Closing Hey. Hey. Who are you faxing so early in the morning? Kind of hard to explain. I don&#39;t have a ton of contact with the Scranton branch. But before I left, I took a box of Dwight&#39;s stationery. So from time to time, I send Dwight faxes from himself from the future. &amp;quot;Dwight, at 8:00 a. m. Today someone poisons the coffee. &amp;quot;Do not drink the coffee. More instructions will follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e08-The Merger</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e08-the-merger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e08-the-merger/</guid>
      <description>s03e08-The Merger The Stamford branch is closing, and everybody&#39;s just packing up their stuff. Andy Bernard made these tasteful hats. That&#39;s the other thing you have to watch out Yo, Tuna. I wanna talk to you about this new boss, Michael Scott. Yeah? So what&#39;s he like? Likes, dislikes, favorite sports, favorite movies, favorite men&#39;s magazines. You know what? I think you just need to meet him. Playing your cards close to the vest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e09-The Convict</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e09-the-convict/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e09-the-convict/</guid>
      <description>s03e09-The Convict Oh, she&#39;s absolutely adorable. He. Oh, sorry. He&#39;s He&#39;s dressed all in pink. That&#39;s his favorite color. Oh, that&#39;s fun for him. Fantastic. Oh, wow, look at that. How cute. Thank you. Oh, may I? Oh, sure. Hey, look at me! I&#39;m a baby. I&#39;m one of those babies from Look Who&#39;s Talking. What am I thinking? Look at all those staplers. What&#39;s a stapler? I don&#39;t even know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e10-A Benihana Christmas</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e10-a-benihana-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e10-a-benihana-christmas/</guid>
      <description>s03e10-A Benihana Christmas Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas No! Why did you bring that here? Don&#39;t worry, she&#39;s dead. Oh, wait. He&#39;s dead. Dwight? What I accidentally ran over it. It&#39;s a Christmas miracle. Well, get it out of here. Relax, okay? And because this is Christmas, I am going to roast this goose and prepare it with a wild rice dressing. Do we have any cayenne pepper in the kitchen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e12-Back from Vacation</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e11-back-from-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e11-back-from-vacation/</guid>
      <description>s03e11-Back from Vacation All right, let&#39;s get started. Oh, first off, we&#39;re supposed to be pushing card stock this week. So, let&#39;s push card stock this week. Also What is this? Tape recorder. For what? For recording. Michael is on vacation and he has asked me to record all meetings and to type up the transcripts. Okay. Karen, any news from that law firm? Yeah, the deal closed yesterday. It&#39;s a six-month commitment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e12-Traveling Salesmen / The Return</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e12-traveling-salesmen-the-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e12-traveling-salesmen-the-return/</guid>
      <description>s03e12-Traveling Salesmen / The Return Angela. What? That was a voicemail that corporate left last night. They did not get our tax forms. Did you send them? They arrived this morning. Are you sure? It is a big deal if Is it a big deal? Is it, Kevin? Do you really not know? Because it is a big deal. Five of us transferred from Stamford. There&#39;s two of us left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e13-The Return</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e13-the-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e13-the-return/</guid>
      <description>s03e13-The Return DWIGHT: I have left Dunder Mifflin after many record-breaking years, and I&#39;m officially on the job market and it&#39;s very exciting. For your convenience, I&#39;ve broken it down into three parts. Professional resume, athletic and special skills resume and Dwight Schrute trivia. DWIGHT: I am ready to face any challenges that might be foolish enough to face me. How would I describe myself? Three words. Hardworking, alpha male, jackhammer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e14-Ben Franklin</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e14-ben-franklin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e14-ben-franklin/</guid>
      <description>s03e14-Ben Franklin Hello, Son. If you&#39;re watching this, that means I&#39;m already dead. Life is a How do you know it&#39;s gonna be a boy? How Would you stop interrupting, please? Yesterday, I was scraping some gunk off my wall sockets with a metal fork and I gave myself the nastiest shock. And when I came to, I had an epiphery. Life is precious. And if I die, I want my son to know the dealio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e15-Phyllis&#39; Wedding</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e15-phyllis-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e15-phyllis-wedding/</guid>
      <description>s03e15-Phyllis&amp;rsquo; Wedding Oh, damn. I lost another file. Gonna have to reboot, again. Hey, Dwight, do you want an Altoid? What do you think? In school, we learned about this scientist who trained dogs to salivate at the sound of a bell by feeding them whenever a bell rang. So, for the past couple weeks, I&#39;ve been conducting a similar experiment. Dwight, want an Altoid? Okay. Altoid? Sure. Mint, Dwight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e16-Business School</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e16-business-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e16-business-school/</guid>
      <description>s03e16-Business School Hey, Kevin. Nice of you to join us. Where were you? My tire blew out on the way here, Michael. I almost died. I went into this skid Pop quiz. What? Why is today a special day? I almost died. Today is a special day because I am being honored as a visiting professor. Special lecturer? Emeritus, how did you put it? You will be a guest speaker in my Emerging Enterprises class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e17-Cocktails</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e17-cocktails/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e17-cocktails/</guid>
      <description>s03e17-Cocktails Can you confirm that the straps are tight? Yes. But this seems a little And now the chains. A lot of people think that magic camp is just for kids. And that&#39;s why so many other people in my class were kids. Self-fulfilling prophecy. It&#39;s really for anybody with a dream and a belief in magic, and a little extra time after school. Magic, magic, magic. And now, Michael the Magic will attempt to escape from extreme bondage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e18-The Negotiation</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e18-the-negotiation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e18-the-negotiation/</guid>
      <description>s03e18-The Negotiation So, do you want to see it or not? I don&#39;t know. They&#39;re, like, Friday night crowds Oh, my God. You&#39;re, like, agoraphobic. Agoraphobic? Yeah. Really. Yeah. You would rather sit on your couch and watch a Phillies game than go out to a movie with your awesome girlfriend. Absolutely correct. Later, Jim. Kev, have a good weekend. Yeah, sure. Bye. Okay, so this is what&#39;s gonna happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e19-Safety Training</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e19-safety-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e19-safety-training/</guid>
      <description>s03e19-Safety Training Good morning, Pam. Oh, welcome back, Andy. Drew. I&#39;m Drew now. Oh, Drew. Sorry. Apology not accepted. Because it wasn&#39;t even necessary in the first place. Several weeks ago, Andy Bernard had an incident. But after five weeks in anger management, I&#39;m back, and I&#39;ve got a new attitude and a new name and a bunch of new techniques for dealing with the grumpies. Morning, Jim. Hey, Andy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e20-Product Recall</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e20-product-recall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e20-product-recall/</guid>
      <description>s03e20-Product Recall It&#39;s kind of blurry. That&#39;s better. Question, what kind of bear is best? That&#39;s a ridiculous question. False. Black bear. Well, that&#39;s debatable. There are basically two schools of thought. Fact, bears eat beets. Oh Bears, beets, Battlestar Galactica. Bears do not What is going on? What are you doing? Last week, I was in a drug store and I saw these glasses. Four dollars. And it only cost me $7 to recreate the rest of the ensemble and that&#39;s a grand total of $11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e21-Women&#39;s Appreciation</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e21-womens-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e21-womens-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>s03e21-Women&amp;rsquo;s Appreciation Hey. Hey. Oh, what&#39;s this? That is a demerit. &amp;quot;Jim Halpert. Tardiness. &amp;quot; Oh. I love it, already. You&#39;ve got to learn, Jim. You are a second in command, but that does not put you above the law. Oh, I understand. And I also have lots of questions. Like, what does a demerit mean? Let&#39;s put it this way. You do not want to receive three of those.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e22-Beach Games</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e22-beach-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e22-beach-games/</guid>
      <description>s03e22-Beach Games Okay, where does it hurt? Just All over. I don&#39;t want to do anything. I&#39;m dying. No, that&#39;s not how it works. You have to point to a specific part of the body. Right there. Abdomen. Menses. Maybe. &amp;quot;The uterus contracts after your egg passes through it. &amp;quot; Not it, I don&#39;t have eggs. So when did this start? About 10 minutes ago. I don&#39;t When I came in with the paperwork?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s03e23-The Job</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e23-the-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s03e23-the-job/</guid>
      <description>s03e23-The Job David Oh, Michael Are we all set? Isn&#39;t our interview tomorrow? Yes. I just happened to be in the neighborhood. Thought I&#39;d drop in and say hello. Just happened to be in midtown Manhattan? Thought I&#39;d catch a show. In the middle of a workday? No. You know what, since I&#39;m here, let me ask you a few questions about the job. Okay. How many people are you interviewing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e01-Fun Run</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e01-fun-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e01-fun-run/</guid>
      <description>s04e01-Fun Run Okay. Well I did not get the job in New-York. But I got the real prize domestic bliss. Jan made me breakfast this morning. Well, she bought the milk. It&#39;s soy. This is why I do it. That&#39;s what I have to come home to. She probably won&#39;t be up for a few hours. This is going be a very good year. Very good. Jan is at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e02-Dunder Mifflin Infinity</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e02-dunder-mifflin-infinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e02-dunder-mifflin-infinity/</guid>
      <description>s04e02-Dunder Mifflin Infinity - Hey, I got you one. - Hey. Thank you. I was gonna grab some chips, you want some? No, thanks. We&#39;re still having lunch today, right? I guess. How dare you? Hey, Toby? What&#39;s this? I just wanna remind everyone about the company rules involving PDA, - or public displays of affection. - Yes Some people in the office have complained. - Oh, really. - About other people engaging in PDA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e03-Launch Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e03-launch-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e03-launch-party/</guid>
      <description>s04e03-Launch Party And the same thing goes for quarterly reports. They&#39;re unreadable. They&#39;re just numbers, and boring, and black. So what I was thinking is that maybe we should have some sort of graphic. Like if we have a bad quarter, put in a storm cloud. And, when we have a good quarter fireworks. Or a race car. Doesn&#39;t have to be a race car. Use your imagination. There&#39;s this cube on the screen, and it bounces around all day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e04-Money</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e04-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e04-money/</guid>
      <description>s04e04-Money Coat! Michael just rent The Devil wears Prada. He has his netflix sent here to the office and he watches them in pieces when things are slow. Steak! Where&#39;s my steak? He&#39;s a big Meryl Streep fan, so I shouldn&#39;t be surprised that he&#39;s identified with her character. Get me Armani. A suit? On the phone. The main company number? &#39;Cause I&#39;m gonna have to Where&#39;s Armani? He&#39;s on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e05-Local Ad</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e05-local-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e05-local-ad/</guid>
      <description>s04e05-Local Ad Yeah, everything! It&#39;s all good! Phyllis. - Dancing babies! - Dancing babies. I love it! We are making a commercial for Dunder Mifflin today. Our first ad ever. Corporate purchased some airtime in local markets to spread the word about Dunder Mifflin Infinity, and they are even sending up a professional ad company to help us make it later, so it&#39;s not too shabby. Best ad ever? Gimme a break Gimme a break Break me off a piece of that I am totally blanking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e06-Branch Wars</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e06-branch-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e06-branch-wars/</guid>
      <description>s04e06-Branch Wars Dunder Mifflin, this is Rolando. Oh yes, she&#39;s been expecting your call. Yeah. - He&#39;s on line one. - Thanks, Ro. Hey, we finally connected. How&#39;s Scranton? I am the regional manager of Dunder-Mifflin Utica branch. Turns out it&#39;s a pretty easy gig when your boss isn&#39;t an idiot and your boyfriend&#39;s not in love with somebody else. Look, All I&#39;m saying is it would be a great opportunity, and we&#39;d love to have you come aboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e07-Survivor Man</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e07-survivor-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e07-survivor-man/</guid>
      <description>s04e07-Survivor Man I really didn&#39;t think I was gonna have a good time but I did. I love camping. Anything can happen Well it wasn&#39;t camping. It was more of a wilderness retreat. - Morning. - Michael. Ryan invited some of the branch managers and Toby into the woods for a &amp;quot;get to know you&amp;quot; weekend. Michael wasn&#39;t invited. Apparently they already knew everything they needed to know about him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e08-The Deposition</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e08-the-deposition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e08-the-deposition/</guid>
      <description>s04e08-The Deposition So the figures show improvement right there, Michael. And again I&#39;ll call back. You never call back. Every time Michael&#39;s in a meeting, he makes me come in and give him a post-it note telling him who&#39;s on the phone. I did it once, and he freaked out. He loved it so much. The thing is, he doesn&#39;t get that many calls. So he has me make them up every ten minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e09-Dinner Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e09-dinner-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e09-dinner-party/</guid>
      <description>s04e09-Dinner Party This is ridiculous. Do you have any idea what time we get out of here? Nobody likes to work late. Least of all, me. - You have plans tonight? - No, I don&#39;t. Remember when you told us not to make plans &#39;cause we were working? Yes, I remember. This is B. S. This is B. S. Why are we here? I am gonna call corporate. Enough is enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e10-Chair Model</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e10-chair-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e10-chair-model/</guid>
      <description>s04e10-Chair Model W. B. Jones is renovating their offices and their cruise are taking up some of the parking spaces we used to get. So we had to park at a satellite parking lot over there. Which just means we get to see more of our lovely street. Tell them what we saw today, Jim. Oh, today we saw a junkyard dog attacking the bones of a rotisserie chicken. Nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e11-Night Out</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e11-night-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e11-night-out/</guid>
      <description>s04e11-Night Out What&#39;s wrong, Michael? I got gum in my hair. - You do. - This just stinks. Don&#39;t touch it. Please, don&#39;t touch it! - You got a ton of dandruff. - Okay, let me be. How&#39;d you do? I was walking in and I noticed something shiny under Stanley&#39;s car. And I gone under seeing what it was and I messed up my hair. All for a stupid piece of tinfoil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e12-Did I Stutter?</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e12-did-i-stutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e12-did-i-stutter/</guid>
      <description>s04e12-Did I Stutter? Everybody, everybody, listen up. I need your ideas now. Ideas, please, right now. Go, go! - Come on! - What you&#39;re talking about? Wet cement outside, it&#39;s drying fast. Come on, this is a lifelong dream. What do I write? Michael, you could put your initials in it. M. G. S. , no. Some idiot named Mark Greg Sputnik will claim credit for it. I don&#39;t Once in a lifetime opportunity, people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e13-Job Fair</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e13-job-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e13-job-fair/</guid>
      <description>s04e13-Job Fair Hey. Ready? Come on! Show me excited. - Yes! - Yeah. I&#39;m pretty excited too. Today I&#39;m headed over to the Job Fair at Valley View High School to find some new interns. Wanna get some fresh blood youthanize this place. - We doin&#39; this thing? - Yeah. Oh, my god, Darryl. You look like Barack Obama. Everybody, I&#39;m dating Barack Obama. - Why you dressed like that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s04e14-Goodbye, Toby</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e14-goodbye-toby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s04e14-goodbye-toby/</guid>
      <description>s04e14-Goodbye, Toby Hello, this is Dwight Schrute. - Hello? - Hello, this is Dwight. Hello? Hello? Yes, we do have that. Hold on one second. - Jim what are you doing? - And how many would you like? - Hang that up right now. - I can get that out to you immediately. It&#39;s an imposter. Don&#39;t do business with him, this is not Dwight Schrute. Dwight left his cell phone on his desk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e01-Weight Loss</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e01-weight-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e01-weight-loss/</guid>
      <description>s05e01-Weight Loss Episode 5x01 &amp;quot;Weight Loss&amp;quot; (1. 01) All right, everybody. This is your last meal. So eat up. From this point forward, you will not use the bathroom. We need to keep our starting weights high. So we can lose more. This summer, corporate is sponsoring a little weight loss contest between the branches. Whichever branch loses the most weight gets 3 extra vacation days. - What should we do with the leftovers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e02-Business Ethics</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e02-business-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e02-business-ethics/</guid>
      <description>s05e02-Business Ethics - Well, I should go. - All right, I&#39;ll tell everybody here that you say hi. No, don&#39;t. I&#39;m mad at them. Why? What happened? Not one of them called to congratulate me on our engagement. That they might be off the hook for, because I didn&#39;t tell them. What? Why not? I just didn&#39;t, you know, want to deal Come on, it won&#39;t be that bad. You know what?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e03-Baby Shower</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e03-baby-shower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e03-baby-shower/</guid>
      <description>s05e03-Baby Shower - Michael? - Yeah. Contractions are coming every 10 minutes. Just remember to keep breathing. - My cervix is ripening. - OK, good. Jan is about to have a baby with a sperm donor. And Michael is preparing for the birth of a watermelon with Dwight. Now, this baby will be related to Michael through delusion. - Michael! My water&#39;s breaking! - OK! OK! What do you do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e04-Crime Aid</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e04-crime-aid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e04-crime-aid/</guid>
      <description>s05e04-Crime Aid - Pam, line 3. - OK, thanks. New york, as it turns out, is very expensive. And I ran out of money. I thought about selling a kidney, but Michael offered to get me a part-time job at corporate. Pamela Of course, now Michael knows where to reach me 16 to 18 hours a week. Miss you, kiddo. Miss you so much. Episode 5x04 &amp;quot;Crime Aid&amp;quot; (1. 00) - That was really fun last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e05-Employee Transfer</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e05-employee-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e05-employee-transfer/</guid>
      <description>s05e05-Employee Transfer You guys look amazing. Stanley, I thought you hated halloween. He wears it so he can sleep at his desk. - Who are you? - Carrie Bradshaw from Sex and the City. - I like your shoes. - Thank you. - Will you help walk me to the fax? - Sure. I got her, I got her, I can help you. - You look amazing. - Inappropriate. Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e06-Customer Survey</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e06-customer-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e06-customer-survey/</guid>
      <description>s05e06-Customer Survey Hey, sport. I heard someone got engaged, you dog! God! Nothing can hurt you now. You&#39;re a man in love! I was there. That dude is not engaged. I&#39;m not a big believer in therapy, but I&#39;ll go into my own pockets to cover his co-pay. Big idea: double wedding. Me, Angela. You, Holly. We would never do that. And if we did, it would be with Jim and Pam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e07-Business Trip</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e07-business-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e07-business-trip/</guid>
      <description>s05e07-Business Trip Did you know that in Morocco it is common to exchange a small gift when meeting somebody for the first time? In Japan, you must always commit suicide to avoid embarrassment. In Italy, you must always wash your hands after going to the bathroom. This is considered to be polite. Why are you telling us this? I am jetting off on an international business trip. - Where you going?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e08-Frame Toby</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e08-frame-toby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e08-frame-toby/</guid>
      <description>s05e08-Frame Toby Are you swallowing them whole? You&#39;re eating them so fast, are they even touching your tongue? Brownies, is it? Pastry cubes made of sugar and fat? No, thanks. I&#39;ll stick with my jerky. - Why&#39;d you come in here? - To socialize. And inform. I&#39;m taking two so I can parcel them up and eat them at my leisure later on. Much healthier. You taking two? Yeah, but one of them is for Toby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e09-The Surplus</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e09-the-surplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e09-the-surplus/</guid>
      <description>s05e09-The Surplus Here are our final actual costs for this year. As you can see, we did pretty well. Yes, I can see That we did indeed. Why don&#39;t you explain this to me like I am an 8-year-old? This is the overall budget for this fiscal year along the x-axis. - Right there. - There&#39;s the &amp;quot;x-axix. &amp;quot; You can see clearly on this page that we have a surplus of $4,300.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e10-Moroccan Christmas</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e10-moroccan-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e10-moroccan-christmas/</guid>
      <description>s05e10-Moroccan Christmas What is this? Happy holidays, Dwight. But do not open it till Christmas. You are so pathetic. How long did this take you? 3 hours? Five minutes, actually. I am a black belt in gift wrapping. No such thing. They don&#39;t give out black belts for things that are stupid. I hope it was worth it, &#39;cause I&#39;m gonna take it apart in about five minutes. I think it&#39;ll take you a little bit longer than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e11-The Duel</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e11-the-duel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e11-the-duel/</guid>
      <description>s05e11-The Duel Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam. I&#39;m sorry. He&#39;s not in yet. Would you like his voicemail? Eat that, Carl Lewis! Angela made several 911 calls about cars going too fast in front of the building, so the police put up a radar gun. It&#39;s actually caused a bit of a traffic hazard. Wow, 13! No, there was wind. - I was just jogging. - There was wind. - I want a do-over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e12-Prince Family Paper</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e12-prince-family-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e12-prince-family-paper/</guid>
      <description>s05e12-Prince Family Paper What&#39;s this? Looks like a red wire. That wasn&#39;t here before. It&#39;s a computer, Dwight. I mean, computers have wires. Yours doesn&#39;t. Doesn&#39;t it? It&#39;s going in a different direction than the other wires. I&#39;m really busy. I can&#39;t talk about this anymore. - Just shut up, Phyllis. - Get outta here. What are you doing? I got 500 feet of red wire at a flea market up by Dunmore High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e13-Stress Relief</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e13-stress-relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e13-stress-relief/</guid>
      <description>s05e13-Stress Relief Last week i gave a fire safety talk. And nobody paid any attention. It&#39;s my own fault for using powerpoint. Powerpoint is boring. People learn in lots of different ways, But experience is the best teacher. Today, smoking is gonna save lives. Does anyone smell anything smoky? Did you bring your jerky in again? Oh, my god! Uh, oh, my god. Fire! Oh, fire! Oh, my goodness. What&#39;s the procedure?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e14-Lecture Circuit (1)</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e14-lecture-circuit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e14-lecture-circuit-1/</guid>
      <description>s05e14-Lecture Circuit (1) This morning, the phone guy comes in, and he shows Michael that our phones have a P. A. function. And then he just left. This is your captain speaking. The office will be flying at an altitude of two stories. Look out your left-hand window, and you will see Vance Refrigeration. I am the ghost of salesmen past. Do not come near me! Yes, Michael Scott for Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e15-Lecture Circuit (2)</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e15-lecture-circuit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e15-lecture-circuit-2/</guid>
      <description>s05e15-Lecture Circuit (2) I am on a lecture circuit. I&#39;m going around to all the branches, and I&#39;m telling them my secret recipe for success. I have now memorized all of your names. Shirty, Mole, Lazy eye, Mexico, Baldy. Then I turn it on and I say, &amp;quot;Prepare yourself for the Utica chain store massacre. &amp;quot; - How&#39;s Jim? - We&#39;re engaged. - My God, I&#39;m so happy for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e16-Blood Drive</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e16-blood-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e16-blood-drive/</guid>
      <description>s05e16-Blood Drive Good morning. Can i help you? Yes,i&#39;m from techstar about a new phone system for you. I was wondering if i could talk to michael scott. I&#39;m sorry. He&#39;s not in right now. Really? He&#39;s never around when i come by. Shoot. They have new phone systems now that can ring directly to a salesman,or someone presses star and they go to accounting. Basically,95% of my job. But i&#39;d like to see a machine that puts out candy for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e17-Golden Ticket</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e17-golden-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e17-golden-ticket/</guid>
      <description>s05e17-Golden Ticket That&#39;s no problem. - Hang up. - Sure. - Knock, knock. - On the phone. - I know you are. Knock, knock. - You can fax it over. Yeah, 5-7-0 - 5-5 - 5-9-1 - 0-1 - 7-4 - 7-5. - &amp;quot;Flive-ling. &amp;quot; That makes us look unprofessional. They would never know it was me. Here we go. Who&#39;s there? - Buddha. - Buddha who? Buddha this bread for me, won&#39;t you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e18-New Boss</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e18-new-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e18-new-boss/</guid>
      <description>s05e18-New Boss Since it is your 15th anniversary at the company, I thought it might be appropriate to begin the festivities with a 15-minute round of applause. - I like it. - Followed by a 15-minute moment of silence. I don&#39;t know. Is it classy enough? Enough with the classy, OK? I just feel like after 15 years at this company Bravo, by the way. That we should celebrate with a classy event, a night to remember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e19-Two Weeks</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e19-two-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e19-two-weeks/</guid>
      <description>s05e19-Two Weeks I had no idea when I got into that car to go to New York that I was going to be quitting. I got on the ramp, and I was like, &amp;quot;two hours, two hours to go. &amp;quot;Feelin&#39; good. Crank some tunes. Should have peed before I left. &amp;quot; Get to the good part. Get up to building. Revolving door broken. So I have to take the normal door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e20-Dream Team</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e20-dream-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e20-dream-team/</guid>
      <description>s05e20-Dream Team You gonna answer that, kev? Right. Thanks. Dunder mifflin. This is kevin. Please hold while i transfer you. Oscar, your mom. Charles is having kevin cover the phones for a while. How do i say this diplomatically? I think kevin is doing exactly as well As anyone might have expected someone like him To perform in a position like that. Please hold. Andy, phone call. No, stay there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e21-The Michael Scott Paper Company</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e21-the-michael-scott-paper-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e21-the-michael-scott-paper-company/</guid>
      <description>s05e21-The Michael Scott Paper Company It&#39;s britney, bitch. And i am back in the form of a new company-- The michael scott paper company. Okay. Not gonna make this one. Love thhair. - Good morning, michael. - Hello. They took away my parking space, But they can&#39;t take away my pride. I would like to invite you all to come along with me On a journey. Welcome to theichael scott paper company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e22-Heavy Competition</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e22-heavy-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e22-heavy-competition/</guid>
      <description>s05e22-Heavy Competition Things are a little slow here, And there&#39;s only so much cold calling you can do in a day. Turns out there&#39;s no limit to the number of cheese puffs Yocan throw at someone&#39;s face. We&#39;re getting pretty good at it. Proudly presents season5 episode22 Andy put down a bunch of deposits On stuff for his wedding with angela, But then she was sleeping with dwight Forseveral years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e23-Broke</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e23-broke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e23-broke/</guid>
      <description>s05e23-Broke It&#39;s 4:30 in the morning. Do you know where your kids are? If you are Ryan&#39;s parents or Pam&#39;s parents or my parents, you do. They&#39;re gonna be in this van. With me. Who am I? Nothing to fear. I am just a 44-year-old guy with a paper route. Time to make the donuts! Come on. No, I promise I won&#39;t do it again. Come on. De-nied! We&#39;ve been making 5:00 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e24-Casual Friday</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e24-casual-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e24-casual-friday/</guid>
      <description>s05e24-Casual Friday At least once a year, i like to bring in Some of my kevin&#39;s famous chili. The trick is to undercook the onions. Everybody is going to get to know each other in the pot. I&#39;m serious about this stuff. I&#39;m up the night before pressing garlic And dicing whole tomatoes. I toast my own ancho chilies. Jesus. It&#39;s a recipe passed down from malones for generations. It&#39;s probably the thing i do best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e25-Cafe Disco</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e25-cafe-disco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e25-cafe-disco/</guid>
      <description>s05e25-Cafe Disco Oh,my god! I can&#39;t believe it! I just won an art contest. Thanks. I still don&#39;t understand why you wanted me to say that. Shut up. I got her! Not cool,dwight. Not cool,man. S05E25 Oh no! I still have the lease On the michael scott paper company, So occasionally i will sneak down here For a little coffee and dancing. I actually dance all the time. Tiptoeing around corporate,it is a ballet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s05e26-Company Picnic</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e26-company-picnic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s05e26-company-picnic/</guid>
      <description>s05e26-Company Picnic Dunder mifflin. This is erin. He&#39;s not available right now. Uh-Huh. Yes. Sure, i&#39;ll give him the message when he gets up. Gets back. Michael had chicken pot pie for lunch. Actually, let me rephrase that. Michael had anentire chicken pot pie for lunch. And-- Let me be more specific. Michael ate an entire family-Sized Chicken pot pie for lunch, And then he promptly fell asleep. So we&#39;re all trying to be very quiet So as to not wake him up before 5:00 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e01-Gossip</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e01-gossip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e01-gossip/</guid>
      <description>s06e01-Gossip Parkour! - Michael-- - Parkour! Parkour! - Extreme! Parkour! - Parkour! This is parkour. Internet sensation of 2004 And it was in one of the bond films. It&#39;s pretty impressive. The goal is to get from point &amp;quot;a&amp;quot; to point &amp;quot;b&amp;quot; as creatively as possible. So technically they are doing parkour As long as point &amp;quot;a&amp;quot; is delusn and point &amp;quot;b&amp;quot; is the hospital. Parkour! - Yeah! Parkour! - Okay, here we go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e02-The Meeting</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e02-the-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e02-the-meeting/</guid>
      <description>s06e02-The Meeting - You wanted to see me? - Yes, Oscar, come on in. Close the door, if you would. Thanks so much for talking to me. Yeah, sure. I&#39;m going in for a procedure today. Is everything okay? It&#39;s routine. I&#39;m just a little bit scared. I&#39;m sure everything will be fine. What&#39;s the procedure, if you don&#39;t mind my asking? It is a colonoscopy. In your experience, what should I be expecting in terms of sensation or emotions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e03-The Promotion</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e03-the-promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e03-the-promotion/</guid>
      <description>s06e03-The Promotion Could you please sign my expense report? No way, no how. Expense reports are a day-to-day item. That is jim&#39;s now. I am exclusively big picture, epic. - Sign this. - Ah, ah, ah. Where&#39;s the &amp;quot;please&amp;quot;? We&#39;re not animals. Sign it. No, not without a &amp;quot;please. &amp;quot; Idiot. I have a complaint about jim. That is not big picture. I would like to file a huge, enormous, massive complaint about the tallest guy in our office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e04-Niagara</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e04-niagara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e04-niagara/</guid>
      <description>s06e04-Niagara **** My stomach&#39;s a little more sensiti lately, so if you wouldn&#39;t mind wearing a little less rfume And if your lunch is especiallpungent, maybe ve it in the break room. We would really preciate it. Pam is constantly throwing up because of the pregnancy. If she eats something the fetus doesn&#39;t like,she is scred. It&#39;s amazing. A three-ounce fetus is calling the shots. It&#39;s so badass. Phyllis,um,if you could switch to a different soap just for a month or two--?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e05-Mafia</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e05-mafia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e05-mafia/</guid>
      <description>s06e05-Mafia The fundamentals of business. The fundamentals of business. Mental is a part of the word. I have underlined it. Because you&#39;re mental if you don&#39;t have a good time. You have to enjoy it. The fun is in it. - Fundamental. - Right. - Get out. - I am. Yes, so it all starts with a handshake. But you can&#39;t just go right to the selling. You need small talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e06-The Lover</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e06-the-lover/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e06-the-lover/</guid>
      <description>s06e06-The Lover They&#39;re back. Oh,yeah. Jim and pam. How was puerto rico? Was it so romantic? - It really was. - Really was. I&#39;m so happy for you. Puerto rico was awesome. Oh,my gosh,the honeymoon was great. We met this other couple at the resort,frank and benny. We hung out with them a lot. Frank and beans. Always makes her laugh. Frank and beans. Is there someone there? Who is there?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e07-Koi Pond</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e07-koi-pond/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e07-koi-pond/</guid>
      <description>s06e07-Koi Pond Welcome,children of the scranton industrial park communities! Yay! Join your gangster pumpkin on his pallet truck of doom. Don&#39;t worry about a thing. Rest assured you will see me later! We are doing a haunted house this halloween, which is actually kind of spooky, because,as legend has it, on this very site there used to be a productive paper company. I am going to scare these kids so bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e08-Double Date</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e08-double-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e08-double-date/</guid>
      <description>s06e08-Double Date - Stanley? - Thank you. Oh,no,no,no. I got a pumpernickel just for you. H and h. You went all the way to new york city to get us bagels? Oh,why,is there a place closer that sells them? This was really nice,dwight. - Thanks. - Thanks. Oh,don&#39;t mention it. You owe me one. You all owe me one. - Good morning,michael. - Good morning,dwight. Hungry? No. I had a fish stick sandwich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e09-Murder</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e09-murder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e09-murder/</guid>
      <description>s06e09-Murder Boom! Boom boom! Broken nose! Boom boom boom! Broken nose! Boom! TOPTOPTHIS YEAR IN MARTIAL ARTS: as we all know,the one thing that thousand-year-old martial arts do all the time is change. How can i pose this to you in a relatable way? You are all members of the yakuza, and you happen to be visiting the lackawanna trolley museum, and you are attacked by triads. How can you hold them off until your clan arrives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e10-Shareholder Meeting</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e10-shareholder-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e10-shareholder-meeting/</guid>
      <description>s06e10-Shareholder Meeting Not again. Bow down before recyclops. Five years ago,corporate said we had to start a recycling program for earth day. So dwight took the lead on that and introduced us to a very close friend of his named recyclops. Happy earth day,everyone,i&#39;m recyclops. Did you know that an old milk carton can be sawed in half and used as a planter? The next year he really stepped things up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e11-Scott&#39;s Tots</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e11-scotts-tots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e11-scotts-tots/</guid>
      <description>s06e11-Scott&amp;rsquo;s Tots You wanted to see me? Yeah. Have a seat. Is it serious? - Andy&#39;s a wittle scawed. - Okay,right there. Right there is the problem. There have been reports around the office that you have been talking baby talk. Why would people say that? Well,I have it on good authority that you said the following. Can you read that back to me? &amp;quot;Andy have a boo-boo tummy. Would you rather me say &amp;quot;hey,guys,my irritable bowel syndrome is flaring up&amp;quot;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e12-Secret Santa</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e12-secret-santa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e12-secret-santa/</guid>
      <description>s06e12-Secret Santa - Attention, everyone! Jim and I, on behalf of - Too loud. - The party planning committee, - Too too loud, too loud. - Have an annou-- But effective. Look. On behalf of jim and I, Merry christmas. Merry christmas. - Good. - My diabolical plot is on hold for christmas. My heart just melts with the sound of children singing. Not really. I&#39;m just tired. The days are short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e13-The Banker</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e13-the-banker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e13-the-banker/</guid>
      <description>s06e13-The Banker But first, an investment banker has to drop by And sign off on our branch. And I&#39;m pretty nervous about it. And I&#39;mMaking some cosmetic tweaks To help create a more appealing environment. Is that dishonest? Well, think of it this way. When you look in the mirror and you see your push-up bra And your fake eyelhes and your makeup, And your press-on nails, The principles that I&#39;m applying to the office Are the same ones that have made lady gaga a star.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e14-Sabre</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e14-sabre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e14-sabre/</guid>
      <description>s06e14-Sabre # I got a big box, yes I do # # I got a big box, how &#39;bout you? # # I got a big box, yes I do # # I got a big box, how &#39;bout you? # I think you don&#39;t know what you&#39;re saying. It is from &amp;quot;sob-ray&amp;quot;, our new owner, And it is to sabre, us. I wonder what&#39;s inside. Scissor me. Dunder mifflin was recently bought By an electronics company named sabre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e15-The Manager and the Salesman</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e15-the-manager-and-the-salesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e15-the-manager-and-the-salesman/</guid>
      <description>s06e15-The Manager and the Salesman I have a reservation in your fair city From February 12th through the 19th, First week of the olympics. Well, we&#39;re looking forward to having you, So let me just pull up your information here. - Okeydoke. - I don&#39;t seem to have it, sir. What? I&#39;m not seeing anything under confirmation. - No-- - could it be under affirmation? You have thousands of those.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e16-The Delivery</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e16-the-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e16-the-delivery/</guid>
      <description>s06e16-The Delivery I just wanted to check and see if there was anything you needed before I went on my maternity leave. (CHUCKLING) Yeah. I&#39;m pregnant. Great. Well, I&#39;ll write up the order. Wait a minute. Okay, thanks. You can&#39;t do that. You cannot exploit your baby for sales. Hey, did I tell you we&#39;re gonna have a baby? (CHUCKLES) Thank you very much. I&#39;m excited Oh. Definitely. No. No!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e18-St. Patrick&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e18-st.-patricks-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e18-st.-patricks-day/</guid>
      <description>s06e18-St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day Nature&#39;s viagra. Two of my favorite joke areas combined. Gonna be a good day. I don&#39;t wanna bring my friends. Why can&#39;t it just be the two of us? Because it&#39;s st. Patrick&#39;s day. People go out in groups. Well, why don&#39;t you invite your friends? Why are you being so weird about this? Stop fighting. Just on st. Patrick&#39;s day, okay? Just one perfect day a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e19-New Leads</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e19-new-leads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e19-new-leads/</guid>
      <description>s06e19-New Leads Hey, jim, jim! Come here. Do you know who that is? - No. - Look at him. Look at him, t-shirt, jeans. - Is it you? - I am flattered. That&#39;s johnny depp. - Where&#39;d you take that? - In my condo complex. Oh, my god, that&#39;s right! I read in people magazine That he was looking for a two-bedroom condo in scranton. I&#39;m flippin&#39; out, man. Hey, jim, jim, Where-where do I find the black pearl?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e20-Happy Hour</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e20-happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e20-happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>s06e20-Happy Hour Okay Work your core! Come on. How many is that? Not counting the last one, Count the last one. Okay, Oh, new record! Okay. Oh, what did you do today? I made a sale. Oh, yeah, sitting on your big, fat butt. All right, that is the number to beat. What do we get if we do &#39;em? My respect. Okay, I&#39;ll make it a little more interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e21-Secretary&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e21-secretarys-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e21-secretarys-day/</guid>
      <description>s06e21-Secretary&amp;rsquo;s Day Nce between a chimichanga, a chalupa, and a tostada? Call me back asap. It&#39;s urgent. [Laughter] This isn&#39;t funny. I don&#39;t talk like that. - [Laughs] Say, &amp;quot;me eat cookie. &amp;quot; - No. I won&#39;t say it. - Why is everyone clumped around accounting? Break it up, you clique. - It&#39;s Kevin as cookie monster from Sesame Street. - Is that the program where all those puppets live in the barrio?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e22-Body Language</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e22-body-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e22-body-language/</guid>
      <description>s06e22-Body Language Buenos dias, erin. Buenos dias, miguel. Hello, dunder-mifflin. No, no, no, no. Solamente, en espaÃ±ol, por favor. I believe that every man, woman, and child in this country Should learn how to speak spanish. They are our neighbors he south, An to cancun. Buenos diaz, jaime. Buenos diaz, miguel. Como estas? Ha ha! Buenos diaz, dwight! Guten tag, herr michael. I don&#39;t understand why michael Is wasting his time with spanish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e23-The Cover-Up</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e23-the-cover-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e23-the-cover-up/</guid>
      <description>s06e23-The Cover-Up - Stop it. - Stop what? You&#39;re talking about me in morse code. Well, you know what? Joke&#39;s on you. &#39;cause I know morse code. Ha! Yeah. That&#39;s what we&#39;re doing. In our very limited free time And with our very limited budget, We went and got a nanny and then we nt out And took a class on a very outmoded And very unnecessary form of communication just so We could talk about you in front of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e24-The Chump</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e24-the-chump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e24-the-chump/</guid>
      <description>s06e24-The Chump Please don&#39;t throw these out. See them all over the office. Toby has been leaving radon kits everywhere, Like he owns the place. The first time I threw mine away, I thought it was an ant trap. But I figured I&#39;d rather live with ants Than with his creepy little disk. The second time I thought it was one of those, You know, the things you turn over, and it moos, Like a cow thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s06e25-Whistleblower</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e25-whistleblower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s06e25-whistleblower/</guid>
      <description>s06e25-Whistleblower Michael Scott, as seen on TV. I saw you on the news, And I want to pinch your tiny wiener. It&#39;s packer! - Oh! Pack-man, I thought you were a girl. Apparently, there are allegations That sabre printer can cause a fire So they asked me to give a statement to the press. I&#39;m like, &amp;quot;what? All right. &amp;quot; So I do it. It&#39;s on TV last night. And it&#39;s in the paper today, and it&#39;s online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e01-Nepotism</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e01-nepotism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e01-nepotism/</guid>
      <description>s07e01-Nepotism - no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no nobody can do shing-a-ling like I do nobody can do the skate like I do nobody can to the boogaloo like I do nobody can do the Philly like I do well, don&#39;t you know I&#39;m gonna skate, I do it ain&#39;t nobody do it but me nobody but me - You&#39;re falling behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e02-Counseling</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e02-counseling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e02-counseling/</guid>
      <description>s07e02-Counseling Late every day this week. We signed Ceecee for the staycare, it&#39;s on the other side of town. The traffic - Why didn&#39;t I think of this before? Did you know that there is a daycare center Opening right here in this building? Is there really? Now that I own the building, I&#39;m looking for new sources of revenue. And a daycare center? Well, I guess it&#39;s not an evil idea, It&#39;s just a regular idea, but there&#39;s no Good laugh for a regular idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e03-Andy&#39;s Play</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e03-andys-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e03-andys-play/</guid>
      <description>s07e03-Andy&amp;rsquo;s Play did sweeney Todd the demon barber of fleet street Did you write this? - No. - Who did? - Stephen sondheim. - Who is he? swing your razor wide, sweeney hold it to to the skies freely flows the blood of those who moralize What the hell is happening? We are the cast of sweeney Todd: The demon barber of fleet street. We open in a couple of weeks at the loose screw playhouse, Here in Scranton, and today, just doing a wee bit of viral marketing, gov&#39;nor!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e04-Sex Ed</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e04-sex-ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e04-sex-ed/</guid>
      <description>s07e04-Sex Ed Hola. Hola. Necesito UN buen worker. TÃº es fuerte. Come on. Â¿que? Â¿que? No vamos con ESE senor. Lo he visto saliendo con muchos otros, Y no vuelven nadie. We don&#39;t go with that man. I&#39;ve seen several men go with that man and not come back. - He perdido amigos - We&#39;ve lost friends No Se lo Que hace con ellos. We don&#39;t know what he does with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e05-The Sting</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e05-the-sting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e05-the-sting/</guid>
      <description>s07e05-The Sting - Look at that, heh, nice. - I love cycling. Andy, I feel like a tourist in my own city. I literally can&#39;t wait to wake up every morning. - Ok. - She is a beauty. - Can&#39;t beat a horse. A horse is a bike that pedals itself. - Oh, look at that, smooth roll. -Yeah - You got it! Lance Armstrong&#39;s bike. - Yes! - His ass was on that seat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e06-Costume Contest</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e06-costume-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e06-costume-contest/</guid>
      <description>s07e06-Costume Contest What about this one? It&#39;s kind a bad ass, right? Just seems kind of crazy in the way I might need right now. I don&#39;t know That&#39;s not yours. Stanley just drunk OJ out of my mug and didn&#39;t seem to realize that wasn&#39;t his hot coffee, so the question has to be asked Is there no limit to what he won&#39;t notice? What&#39;s a seven letter word for purse?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e07-Christening</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e07-christening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e07-christening/</guid>
      <description>s07e07-Christening I know a lot of us have been feeling under the weather lately, it&#39;s that time of year and according to a study done by the University of Arizona, they discovered that your keyboards have hundreds of time more bacteria per square inch Than a toilet seat. That&#39;s true. That&#39;s true. I dated her mama. And you know what? Stop. One of the simplest ways to cut down On the spread of germs is to use something Called the vampire cough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e08-Viewing Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e08-viewing-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e08-viewing-party/</guid>
      <description>s07e08-Viewing Party They caught the Scranton strangler. They trapped him in his house. And then photographing them, Is believed to be inside. Police have now surrounded The apartment complex. Police have surrounded. And we now see what appears to be A SWAT van pulling up. Swat swat&#39;s arriving. It is unknown he is armed with any They should do that thing where they play The really good music to get him to come out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e09-WUPHF.com</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e09-wuphf.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e09-wuphf.com/</guid>
      <description>s07e09-WUPHF.com - Uh-oh. Okay, okay, nobody panic. Listen up, listen up. Everyone, follow me to the shelter. We&#39;ve got enough food for 14 days. After that, we have a difficult conversation. - My bad. Space Heater and Fan were both on high, plugged into the same outlet, so - uh, it&#39;s saying the server went down? Does Anybody know that password? &#39;cause otherwise, we can&#39;t do any work. - Uhtry &amp;quot;password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e10-China</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e10-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e10-china/</guid>
      <description>s07e10-China Why? That&#39;s all it takes. all feet, no hands and I&#39;ll have the pededexterity of a chimp and you&#39;ll be sitting there like an idiot. Okay, here we go. Ah, yes. - Do you mind? - I&#39;m sorry, Pam. Allow me to write you an apology letter. You don&#39;t have to do that. - D-e-a oops, space, &amp;quot;a. Dear&amp;quot; thank you, hands. Nothing else in the universe can do what you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e11-Classy Christmas</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e11-classy-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e11-classy-christmas/</guid>
      <description>s07e11-Classy Christmas Got it. Okay, let&#39;s go. I&#39;m freezing. People, wait, wait, wait. Come back, come back. One fun one. We&#39;re gonna do a fun one. One Charlie&#39;s angels. One. Let&#39;s go. Okay, this is just a Christmas card from your paper supplier. No one&#39;s putting this on their fridge. Ooh, I got it, you guys, how &#39;bout this Michael, what if all the boys are on one side, all the girls are on the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e13-Ultimatum</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e13-ultimatum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e13-ultimatum/</guid>
      <description>s07e13-Ultimatum Next stop, secretary **, we&#39;ll read the minutes for Sunday&#39;s meeting. Minutes from previous meeting, oh, knights of the night - No! Jim, hey. - Oh. This meeting is for knights of the night only. Knights of the night are volunteer crime patrollers. We&#39;re often compared to the guardian angels, but we could not be more different from them. Seriously, we are nothing like the guardian angels. I mean, broad strokes purposes, sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e14-The Seminar</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e14-the-seminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e14-the-seminar/</guid>
      <description>s07e14-The Seminar I&#39;m not picking on you at all. You&#39;re English, correct? Yeah, big time, yeah. I&#39;m working on an English character. Would you mind gi it&#39;s called Reginald Pooftah. Ooh! David Brent, my liege. How are you? - Michael Scott. - Oh, there you go. I do characters as well. I got a Chinese fella. He&#39;s called ho me [Bleep]. That&#39;s what it sounds like. [Laughing] - Herrow! Herrow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e15-The Search</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e15-the-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e15-the-search/</guid>
      <description>s07e15-The Search Everybody, can I please have your attention? Ryan and I have a huge announcement. Oh my gosh. Wow. Over the weekend, Ryan Bailey Howard and I got divorced. - Sweet. - Free ring. Divorced? Just so you know, it&#39;s totally amicable. We&#39;re fine. We don&#39;t need people here to take sides. The last thing that we want is any kind of drama. Wait, I Can you back up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e16-PDA</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e16-pda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e16-pda/</guid>
      <description>s07e16-PDA Hey. How are you doing? Been thinking about my grandmother a lot. Yeah. She was about to turn 97. At least she lived a very long and I&#39;m sure very happy life. Got you this card. When you&#39;re ready, we all signed it. We just wanted you to know we&#39;re thinking about you. Thank you. &amp;quot;Congratulations, Darryl. Let&#39;s get wasted. &amp;quot;Have fun today, big guy. &amp;quot;Aww, yeah. Party time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e17-Threat Level Midnight</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e17-threat-level-midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e17-threat-level-midnight/</guid>
      <description>s07e17-Threat Level Midnight I got a delivery for you. Leave it at reception. I&#39;m supposed to deliver this one in person. Clean up on aisle five. After three years of writing, one year of shooting, four years of reshooting, and two years of editing, I have finally completed my movie, Threat Level Midnight. [Cheerful music] - Erin, Erin - Yes? - What are you doing? - Guys Did you guys know that our own Michael Scott has made a movie and that he maybe will let us watch it, but only if everybody&#39;s dying to see it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e18-Todd Packer</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e18-todd-packer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e18-todd-packer/</guid>
      <description>s07e18-Todd Packer I have the best stock survival shelter in north eastern Pennsylvania. But everything is a **life. So I must eat and then replace everything that is about to expire. It&#39;s nice not to have to plan my meals. You&#39;re eating eight-year-old tomatoes. They&#39;re still good for another week. You know, I think I might have some type of cheese in the back of my fridge you might like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e19-Garage Sale</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e19-garage-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e19-garage-sale/</guid>
      <description>s07e19-Garage Sale Race fan, huh? No. Everybody assumes I am. I always get them as gifts. Oh. Dunder Mifflin is having our first ever garage sale. Like many Americans, we realized we had a lot of things that we didn&#39;t really need. And $. 10 of every dollar is going into the party fund, so we can throw parties for ourselves. People, look alive! It&#39;s showtime! Doors open in three Two One!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e20-Training Day</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e20-training-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e20-training-day/</guid>
      <description>s07e20-Training Day - A sombrero, please? - All right. - So just you tonight? - Actually, I am meeting somebody, but I&#39;m a little bit early. Leaving my company. After 19 years. I&#39;ll drink to that! - I&#39;m starting at a company this week. - Oh, really? To beginnings and endings. And to middles, the unsung heroes. And to moms. To moms of the troops. Do not tell my fiancee I&#39;m drinking on a Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e21-Michael&#39;s Last Dundies</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e21-michaels-last-dundies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e21-michaels-last-dundies/</guid>
      <description>s07e21-Michael&amp;rsquo;s Last Dundies It is 6 AM, and Deangelo and I are about to go house to house to give everybody their Dundies nomination certificate just like the oscars. Yes. And this happens every year? Every year this happens. You have a lot to learn, my friend. Well, you know, why don&#39;t we try it, and if it goes good, it&#39;ll be part of my tradition. Why are you even saying that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e22-Goodbye, Michael</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e22-goodbye-michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e22-goodbye-michael/</guid>
      <description>s07e22-Goodbye, Michael Well, I&#39;m moving to Colorado to start my new life with Holly. Just up here getting used to the altitude. - Michael? - Yes? I&#39;ve got a treat for you. Thank you. Like a butler. Colorado specialty-- Rocky Mountain oysters. Wow, those do not taste like oysters. That&#39;s because they&#39;re not oysters. They&#39;re bull testicles! I cut them off fresh this morning! Sick freak. What is wrong with you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e23-The Inner Circle</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e23-the-inner-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e23-the-inner-circle/</guid>
      <description>s07e23-The Inner Circle So, coasting time. It&#39;s officially over. Big changes are coming, and they&#39;re coming fast. And if you don&#39;t like them, this is called a door, you can walk right through it, all right? I&#39;m not here to be your friend. I like my life outside of this place. I live to leave at 5:00. Change number one: Darryl. Per your request, the company is sending you to business school at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e24-Dwight K. Schrute, (Acting) Manager</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e24-dwight-k.-schrute-acting-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e24-dwight-k.-schrute-acting-manager/</guid>
      <description>s07e24-Dwight K. Schrute, (Acting) Manager We can get Deangelo flowers. No, you can&#39;t get flowers for someone who&#39;s in a coma. They&#39;ll wilt before he wakes up. - Yeah, that&#39;s true. - Good point. All in favor of the baskets full of chocolates, Teddy bears, and balloons. Wait, wait. All in favor of the knapsack filled with canned goods, chainsaw, gasoline, and emergency radio in case he wakes up post-apocalypse Nope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s07e25-Search Committee</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e25-search-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s07e25-search-committee/</guid>
      <description>s07e25-Search Committee It&#39;s a beautiful morning at Dunder Mifflin-- Or as I like to call it Great Bratton. Keep it running. Do I love being manager? I love my kids. I love real estate. I love ceramics. I love my job. I-I love wrestling. Find out what language this is. Okay. Team building. On this side of the room, Stanley, Phyllis, Jim, Ted, Elroy. On this side of the room, Pam, Meredith, Phyllis, Creed He never called a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e01-The List</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e01-the-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e01-the-list/</guid>
      <description>s08e01-The List Oh, for God&#39;s sake. &amp;quot;Planking&amp;quot; is a very stupid and dangerous trend. Basically you lie like a plank in weird places. That&#39;s it. Sometimes you get run over. Welcome to the Internet. Planking is one of those things where, hey, you either get it or you don&#39;t. And I don&#39;t. But I am so excited to be a part of it. - After you, my good sir. - No, I insist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e02-The Incentive</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e02-the-incentive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e02-the-incentive/</guid>
      <description>s08e02-The Incentive Hey, so this isn&#39;t matching up with this. So I&#39;m not sure which one is right. Can you just hand down the original for me. - Yes, me do. - All right. Hey, what were you saying before about the paperwork? Me doing now! Go. Stop worry. Kevin, do you feel okay? Me feel good. Body strong. Sleep big last night. Yeah, I think we should get him to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e03-Lotto</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e03-lotto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e03-lotto/</guid>
      <description>s08e03-Lotto Back orders and you never call them. - Can you believe this? - There&#39;s a dog in the car. You can&#39;t leave a dog in a parked car! Snowboarder, it figures. Dude, snowboarders ain&#39;t animals? I bet this guy didn&#39;t leave his weed in the car. Okay, we have to do something because this is incredibly dangerous. Oscar, is not that hard out. A car parked in the sun is like a toast oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e04-Garden Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e04-garden-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e04-garden-party/</guid>
      <description>s08e04-Garden Party Hey. So we saw the new billboard. Yeah? Pretty cool, huh? What better way to announce our new, slightly lower prices than with an ad campaign? And what better face for an ad campaign than our new regional manager? How&#39;d it look? You&#39;ve seen it, right? No. Andy, somebody defaced it. What? How? Morning, Stanley. There&#39;s this thing that people tend to do with billboards. How do I put this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e05-Spooked</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e05-spooked/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e05-spooked/</guid>
      <description>s08e05-Spooked Approved! from South park! It&#39;s genius! I&#39;m I decided to prescreen all the Halloween costumes this year. I&#39;ve three simple rules. Don&#39;t be offensive, don&#39;t be cliche, and don&#39;t take the first two rules too seriously. The gorilla from Rise of the Planet of the Apes. The one who sacrifices his life. Oh! Wow. Spoiler alert! It&#39;s been out for ages, man. Costume vetoed. Yeahlt&#39;s, uh Somebody&#39;s already called that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e06-Doomsday</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e06-doomsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e06-doomsday/</guid>
      <description>s08e06-Doomsday Hey, everybody! It&#39;s closing time! You all gotta go home but you can stay here. Closing time Every office needs an end of the day tradition. Something that tells you that the day is over. Otherwise, you go home and the night just feels like more day, it&#39;s weird. - Closing time - Tell me that you&#39;re okay. One last call so finish your whiskey and beer Oh, my boss is singing closing time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e07-Pam&#39;s Replacement</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e07-pams-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e07-pams-replacement/</guid>
      <description>s08e07-Pam&amp;rsquo;s Replacement - Erin, hey. - Yeah. In two minutes, I want you to come in to this meeting and tell me that I have a really important phone call. I&#39;m not gonna take it because I want him to know how important the meeting is to me. Who&#39;s calling? Nobody. Just say that Just make it up that I have a phone call and I&#39;m gonna refuse to take it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e08-Gettysburg</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e08-gettysburg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e08-gettysburg/</guid>
      <description>s08e08-Gettysburg The Sabre code of conduct outlines the governing principles key to establishing and maintaining trust with - our employees, clients - Oh, my God. Kill me! Hey! All right, obviously we&#39;re all gonna die. But we gotta get through this, so, Gabe Go ahead. It&#39;s okay. Is it okay with you? Because if it&#39;s not, you work for me, so &amp;quot;Comply with all applicable laws, regulations, &amp;quot;policies, and contracts governing our business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e09-Mrs. California</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e09-mrs.-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e09-mrs.-california/</guid>
      <description>s08e09-Mrs. California Oh, a little help. Wow, your hair is really thinning. Standing as proven to be healthier increases productivity and just looks cooler. Picture someone doing something heroic. Now, was he sitting or standing? Not counting FDR. Every second you sit there is an hour off your life. Look at all of you. I feel like you&#39;re in suicide cult. No, no, no. You&#39;re way off on that one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e10-Christmas Wishes</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e10-christmas-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e10-christmas-wishes/</guid>
      <description>s08e10-Christmas Wishes Christmas time is here! Wow! Thanks, guys. That sounded amazing. Hi, I&#39;m * Bernard and I am the first office Santa ever to make holiday wishes come true. Who&#39;s excited to get their holiday wishes? Holiday wishes What&#39;s that, Stanley? We know exactly what holiday you&#39;re referring to. It is important to be mindful of all belief systems at our holiday party. I&#39;ve been here 18 years and I&#39;ve suffered through some weird, thematic christmases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e11-Trivia</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e11-trivia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e11-trivia/</guid>
      <description>s08e11-Trivia Oh, yeah. - Aw! - Knew it! Knew it! As soon as I heard that wrapper. You really have to say &amp;quot;oh yeah,&amp;quot; every time you eat a candy bar? I can&#39;t help it, Oscar. It&#39;s just really good. Oh, yeah. All right, not bad at all. I think we can beat So let&#39;s try again. Get it all out now if you have to. It was a raccoon eating a hamburger like a person!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e12-Pool Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e12-pool-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e12-pool-party/</guid>
      <description>s08e12-Pool Party Oh What is this? A A meatball? Really? It&#39;s always more fun to mess with Dwight with an audience. That was usually Pam. So, now that she&#39;s out, I had to find someone else. Turns out that Stanley is quite the comedy fan. But not everything makes him laugh. He has very specific tastes. Through a painstaking process of trial and error, I found out what he likes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e13-Jury Duty</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e13-jury-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e13-jury-duty/</guid>
      <description>s08e13-Jury Duty Val, I need this space. All right, guys, clear out. Everybody out. Promise me you&#39;re going to clean up. I can&#39;t promise what I&#39;m going to do or not do. Promise me that-- Obviously I&#39;m going to clean up. Stress is like the uptight mayor of a town who&#39;s saying, &amp;quot;hey, we&#39;re uptight, you can&#39;t dance. &amp;quot; And then you have to be like, &amp;quot;oh, yeah, mayor stress?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e14-Special Project</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e14-special-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e14-special-project/</guid>
      <description>s08e14-Special Project Oh, look who&#39;s back reporting for duty. Hey, guys. Hey. Hey, Pam, ah! Look what I can do now that she&#39;s no longer pregnant. Bam, bam, bam, bam. Are you glad to be back? Yeah-- Yeah, I mean I could have used another week or three. You still had eight weeks more than we did. Well, it&#39;s not exactly a vacation. - Hello, everyone. - Hey. Remember? Little old me, hi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e15-Tallahassee</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e15-tallahassee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e15-tallahassee/</guid>
      <description>s08e15-Tallahassee Today is the first day of Sabre&#39;s new project: Develop a chain of retail stores. I am meeting my new boss, Nellie Bertram. Head of Special Projects. Work starts at 9:00. Sabre HQ is 30 minutes away, driving the speed limit. Giving everyone 20 minutes to shower, plus 50 for Jim to style his hair, between her room and the lobby, We&#39;re already 20 minutes late. Wake up! Hey, hey, hey, hey!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e16-After Hours</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e16-after-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e16-after-hours/</guid>
      <description>s08e16-After Hours Hey, Angela. Do you wanna see a picture of Philip wearing those little booties you got us? So cute. Hey, you guys wanna see a picture of Gerald wearing *? He refused to go* is all he wants to do. Oscar thinks having a dog is just like having a baby. News flash, if you didn&#39;t carry it around in your belly for nine months, it isn&#39;t your kid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e17-Test The Store</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e17-test-the-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e17-test-the-store/</guid>
      <description>s08e17-Test The Store Today is the test launch day for the inaugural Sabre store. And I, Dwight Truth I&#39;m in charge of the entire operation. If I can prove myself today and the store is a hit with the media and Nellie sees this, the vice presidency is mine. Hey are you holding this chair? &#39;Cause I feel like - Yes. Yes. Yes. - I&#39;m gonna fall off. I&#39;m not wearing the right shoes for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e18-Last Day In Florida</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e18-last-day-in-florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e18-last-day-in-florida/</guid>
      <description>s08e18-Last Day In Florida Okay. Bye. Everyone stop what you&#39;re doing. I have terrible news. Dwight is no longer with us. What? He&#39;s gone, damn it! He&#39;s been promoted to VP of Sabre retail, and he&#39;s staying in Florida forever. So He&#39;s alive. Yeah. That was him on the phone. He sounds wonderful. Well, the way you said it made it sound like he was dead. How could I have been more clear?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e19-Get The Girl</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e19-get-the-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e19-get-the-girl/</guid>
      <description>s08e19-Get The Girl This is Pam. Oh, my God, are you sure? Uh, okay. Okay, we&#39;ll be right there. Everybody, the balloon is falling. Nice. There&#39;s this balloon that has been floating in the rafters of the warehouse for, like, ever. And, okay, it&#39;s not it doesn&#39;t sound cool. You just have to see it. Well, I guess it doesn&#39;t look that cool either. But it&#39;s been up there a long time, so it&#39;s become a pretty big deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e20-Welcome Party</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e20-welcome-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e20-welcome-party/</guid>
      <description>s08e20-Welcome Party Hey Jim. Stanley&#39;s back from the hospital today. - Can you sign his card? - Oh, great. &amp;quot;Glad they didn&#39;t mix up your tonsillectomy with a moustachectomy. &amp;quot; Oh, that&#39;s not good. Oh, because your jokes are all hilarious. It&#39;s nice. It&#39;s funny. It mentions his tonsillectomy and makes a funny little joke about his moustache. Stanley doesn&#39;t have a moustache. Yeah, he does. Pam, hit the brakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e21-Angry Andy</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e21-angry-andy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e21-angry-andy/</guid>
      <description>s08e21-Angry Andy Woo! Wow, it is raining cats and dogs out there. Holy moly. Phyllis says the same So I promised everyone that if she says them all by noon today, I will send out for hot chocolates. So how&#39;s the drive in? Oh, nobody knows how to drive in the rain. You don&#39;t say? Yeah, you know the roads are actually the slickest in the first half hour? Oh, the plants are gonna love this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e22-Fundraiser</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e22-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e22-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>s08e22-Fundraiser No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no - No! - Okay, fine. Ryan. Is something the matter? Smokey&#39;s dead. Smokey the bear? Smokey Robinson, Pam. He died, like, an hour ago. I guess I&#39;m the first to know. Wow, that&#39;s terrible. I really liked him. Oh, you liked him? That&#39;s nice. Did you &amp;quot;like&amp;quot; when he changed the course of American music like, two or three times?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e23-Turf War</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e23-turf-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e23-turf-war/</guid>
      <description>s08e23-Turf War Man, my delts are blasted. I wish they had a chart for how much protein powder to scoop. For a 180 pound man with no fat. Protein powder, huh? You cut it with water? Why don&#39;t you just take estrogen? There you go, boys. See how papa takes care of you? Mwah. I remember when people thought biceps were all that. They&#39;d flex them all night at the discotheque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s08e24-Free Family Portrait Studio</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e24-free-family-portrait-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s08e24-free-family-portrait-studio/</guid>
      <description>s08e24-Free Family Portrait Studio Hello, my name&#39;s Oscar, I&#39;m an accountant at Scranton, Pennsylvania, and I&#39;m gay. And I&#39;m here to tell you, that yes, it does get better. - When I was younger - What, what&#39;s he doing? - Stretching at younger gays. - Oh No, it&#39;s just a way to tell young people no matter how hard it gets for them, there&#39;s a brave future ahead. - With you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e01-The New Guys</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e01-the-new-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e01-the-new-guys/</guid>
      <description>s09e01-The New Guys Andy&#39;s coming back today. Andy&#39;s coming back today. Ha! Andy&#39;s coming back today. David Wallace sent him on an outward-bound wilderness adventure for a whole month to make him more decisive and confident. He sent his own son too. And the counselor said they both grew up big time. How was my summer? It was pretty mixed. I invented a new power drink made of beet run-off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e02-Roy&#39;s Wedding</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e02-roys-wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e02-roys-wedding/</guid>
      <description>s09e02-Roy&amp;rsquo;s Wedding The building&#39;s custodian is on vacation for the month, and Dwight is too chip to hire a replacement. So, instead, we&#39;re living in filth, but, not for long because I have created the chore wheel. Oh, yeah. Can I spin first? Well, it doesn&#39;t spin. We&#39;ll just move the wheel one notch each morning, and you see what chore you get that day. A wheel is supposed to spin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e03-Andy&#39;s Ancestry</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e03-andys-ancestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e03-andys-ancestry/</guid>
      <description>s09e03-Andy&amp;rsquo;s Ancestry Good morning, Dwight. Who are you? Who am I? I&#39;m Jim. We&#39;ve been working together for 12 years. Weird joke, Dwight. You&#39;re not Jim. Jim&#39;s not Asian. You seriously never noticed? Hey, hats off to you for not seeing race. All right then, Jim. Uh, why don&#39;t you tell me about that sale that you made yesterday? Uh, Wellington Systems? Sold them ten cases of 24-pound letter stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e04-Work Bus</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e04-work-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e04-work-bus/</guid>
      <description>s09e04-Work Bus All right, everybody. Great season of softball, I&#39;m super proud of you, guys. And I think you&#39;re gonna like this little highlight reel that I&#39;ve put together. Dunder Mifflin! Andy Bernard presents Summer Softball, epic fails! Fail. Fail. - That&#39;s me. - Fail. Is this like a blooper reel? A blooper reel? What is this, 2005? Do I look like Bob Saget? Fail! Who&#39;s this guy? Meow, meow, meow, meow meow, meow, meow, meow Look at him dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e05-Here Comes Treble</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e05-here-comes-treble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e05-here-comes-treble/</guid>
      <description>s09e05-Here Comes Treble This year I decided to really get into the spirit of Halloween. *** decision I&#39;ve ever made. My *** head went into the pumpkin no problem - It won&#39;t ***. - but I can&#39;t get it out. Try again. I mean, I could try destroying the pumpkin No! No! No! No! Please! But as Jim and I discovered No! any blow to the pumpkin itself could prove fatal to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e06-The Boat</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e06-the-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e06-the-boat/</guid>
      <description>s09e06-The Boat Can you guys come with me for a minute? I know you saw me with the Senator. I think I&#39;m in love, possibly for the first time. So, yes, Senator Lipton and I are having an affair. I hope that I can count on your sensitivity, maturity, and discretion. Why? All right, good. Yeah, just sell it and get the best price you can, okay? Or we can hope for a holiday rally?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e07-The Whale</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e07-the-whale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e07-the-whale/</guid>
      <description>s09e07-The Whale Uh what else? I&#39;ve seen Dirty Dancing like 10 times. Breaks my heart every time, you know? - Whoa. - Andy. That Swayze sure can dance dirty. Don&#39;t you have any sunblock? No, Walter J has been hoarding it. You want to worry about a part of my body, worry about my eyes. They&#39;re like two flaming meatballs in my skull. Last week Andy set sail for the Bahamas to sell his family&#39;s boat, and he took his brother but not me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e08-The Target</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e08-the-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e08-the-target/</guid>
      <description>s09e08-The Target Yesterday Angela may or may not have figured out that I&#39;m having an affair with her husband. So I just have to wait and see. When she comes in, if she&#39;s cold and awkward and cruel to me, then great, it&#39;s business as usual. Good morning. Oscar Can I ask you a question? Of course, ask me a que-- questions. Is it cool in here to you? Yes, a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e09-Dwight Christmas</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e09-dwight-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e09-dwight-christmas/</guid>
      <description>s09e09-Dwight Christmas I&#39;m having second thoughts about one of the shirts I packed. The blue one with the stripes. I&#39;m sure it&#39;s fine. It&#39;s a blue shirt. Well, yeah, but I&#39;m wondering if it&#39;s too blue. Like, am I making a statement with the blueness? I am leaving early today for Philly, because tomorrow is the first day of my new job. So I figure I&#39;d get in at 5:00, check into a hotel at about 6:00 so I can get a real good night of restless sleep and nervous puking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e10-Lice</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e10-lice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e10-lice/</guid>
      <description>s09e10-Lice To me, the Sixers are a five seat tops. I think they&#39;re going to the Conference finals. - No. - Bynum, an obvious monster. At three-point shooting, don&#39;t even-- I bit my lip at lunch today. Sucks. Anyway, I just don&#39;t see it. The Knicks are tough. - The Nets are tough. - Oh, the Nets are super tough. Now I have this big bump on my lip that hurts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e11-Suit Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e11-suit-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e11-suit-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>s09e11-Suit Warehouse _ Stone &amp;amp; Son Suit Warehouse recently lost their paper provider. They&#39;re a family-owned business. Jim and I used to clean up at those. We&#39;d go in pretending to be family-- brothers. We did it at a family-owned law firm, at a family-owned construction company, and a family-owned motorcycle store. Jim and Dwight Shrupert. - I was the dynamic - Yeah! Likeable winner that was doted upon by mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e12-Customer Loyalty</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e12-customer-loyalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e12-customer-loyalty/</guid>
      <description>s09e12-Customer Loyalty We gotta clear out this cabinet, people. A lot of these are dead accounts. &amp;quot;Scranton Mimeograph Corp&amp;quot;? I don&#39;t think we&#39;re doing business with them anytime soon. That&#39;s odd. A letter from Robert Dunder. &amp;quot;A valuable artifact has come into my possession. I have hidden it until such time as a person of strong intellect may safely recover it. This golden chalice is of immeasurable historical and religious significance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e13-Junior Salesman</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e13-junior-salesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e13-junior-salesman/</guid>
      <description>s09e13-Junior Salesman Hey, Brian, you got a sec? Yeah. I know what you&#39;re gonna say. It&#39;s it&#39;s all right. No, I heard you got in trouble. - I feel awful. - It&#39;s fine. It was my first slipup in nine years of miking you. Dunder Mifflin. This is Erin. Well, thanks for being a good friend. Sure, anytime. Uh, how about you and Jim? - Everything squared away? - Yeah, mostly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e14-Vandalism</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e14-vandalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e14-vandalism/</guid>
      <description>s09e14-Vandalism Have you seen Darryl? He&#39;s around here, somewhere. Hmm. Yeah, Darryl&#39;s here. So is Santa Claus. It&#39;s just a regular Thursday. Neither guy is here. And it&#39;s Friday. Welcome to me and Darryl&#39;s World of Lies. Nobody knows it yet, but Darryl already started working in Philly. So now he has to sneak out of here like the sneakiest little sneaky sneak you ever saw. And I&#39;m his helper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e15-Couples Discount</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e15-couples-discount/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e15-couples-discount/</guid>
      <description>s09e15-Couples Discount Hey. I feel so lucky we&#39;re in the same city for Valentine&#39;s Day. It&#39;s like magic. Or it&#39;s like me getting on my hands and knees and begging my partners to switch a Tuesday for a Thursday. Alakazam. By the way, they do need an extra day next week. And poof, he disappears. Hey. Wanna play hooky today? Oh, maybe. What do you got in mind? We can do anything you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e16-Moving On</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e16-moving-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e16-moving-on/</guid>
      <description>s09e16-Moving On No. You lied to me, Andy! You pretended to be in this office for three months, and you were sailing on your boat! - I resent that. I never lied to you. Really? &amp;quot;Hey, David, all is good in Scranton, P. A. &amp;quot; And all was good in Scranton, P. A. , that day. &amp;quot;By the way, Oscar says hi. &amp;quot; Oscar says hi all the time. He says all kinds of greetings hi, hello, hola.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e17-The Farm</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e17-the-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e17-the-farm/</guid>
      <description>s09e17-The Farm Hold it! New glasses. Dwight, what a ridiculous, fancy clown you are. I am dressed according to the Schrute codes of mourning. My aunt Shirley has died. Oh, Dwight, I&#39;m so sorry. Were you guys close? I would say that she raised me, but let&#39;s not kid each other. I raised myself. She was, however, the closest thing I had to a mother. My actual mother was very cold and distant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e18-Promos</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e18-promos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e18-promos/</guid>
      <description>s09e18-Promos Oh, oh. She&#39;s doing it again. Phyllis has gotten into audiobooks. And lately she&#39;s been listening to 50 Shades Of Grey, which, if you don&#39;t know what it is, - it&#39;s a book about, uh, um-- - It&#39;s porn. Yeah. Seriously? This is unacceptable. It&#39;s officially a hostile work environment. Why? Somebody just needs to get her attention, tell her it&#39;s not okay to do this in public. Be careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e19-Stairmageddon</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e19-stairmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e19-stairmageddon/</guid>
      <description>s09e19-Stairmageddon What the hell? No, this is not happening. Didn&#39;t you get the memo? It&#39;s Stairmageddon. Come on, Stanley! Dwight is having maintenance done on the elevator today, and he was really on top of it. Weeks ago, he started the Stairmageddon awareness campaign. The idea was to get us prepared, both mentally and physically, for a day that hopefully comes once in 100 years. It&#39;s a &amp;quot;mageddon!&amp;quot; Come on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e20-Paper Airplane</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e20-paper-airplane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e20-paper-airplane/</guid>
      <description>s09e20-Paper Airplane Oh! Hey, champions. Good morning. Quarterfinals in an hour. I hope you had some sleep, because I&#39;m gonna be hunting your nightmares tonight. I did. I got some really good sleep. - Did you? - Zzz. Yesterday was the first round of a branch-wide paper airplane contest. It was being sponsored by Weyerhammer Paper in an effort to get us to sell more of their new product, Airstream Deluxe A4, the Cadillac of paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e21-Livin&#39; the Dream</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e21-livin-the-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e21-livin-the-dream/</guid>
      <description>s09e21-Livin&amp;rsquo; the Dream I&#39;m taking some time off from work well, my other work because we needed it. It&#39;s great. The phone&#39;s been ringing off the hook. The guys in Philly are kind of going nuts. But that doesn&#39;t matter. This does. It&#39;s the only thing that matters. We&#39;ve had some really nice days together. Mm-hmm. Nice morning, too. Beesly. Oh, my God. Hey. Which tie makes me look like a guy who likes sofas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e22-A.A.R.M.</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e22-a.a.r.m./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e22-a.a.r.m./</guid>
      <description>s09e22-A.A.R.M. &amp;quot;The tea in Nepal is very hot. &amp;quot; &amp;quot;But the coffee in Peru is much hotter. &amp;quot; Last week, I finally became permanent Manager of Dunder Mifflin Scranton! My first project: Increase security. I got these doors from a jewelry store that had recently gone out of business. Now they&#39;re protecting America&#39;s real treasure Paper! Every morning, I email the day&#39;s security codes. Something that&#39;s been really missing from my life has been writing secret codes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office-s09e23-Finale</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e23-finale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/02/s09e23-finale/</guid>
      <description>s09e23-Finale _ The documentary series finished airing ages ago. Why is PBS sending another crew? We&#39;re getting bonus footage for the DVD. Pfft. Nobody buys DVDs anymore. It&#39;ll be a pledge gift. PBS The propaganda wing of Bill and Melinda Gates and viewers like you. In the past year I&#39;ve consolidated the entire Scranton paper market regained the White Pages, the district, the county, we supply them all. I&#39;m getting married tomorrow afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>