<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019s on Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019s on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>30 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-30/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Watching movies from Netflix The Hulk Marvel. Do you like Marvel? I don&#39;t have any time to see all of the movies. You haven&#39;t seen the Avengers: Endgame yet? I like Iron Man. I like happy endings not bad endings. Does your wife like watching the same movies? She likes movies like love movies or romantic movies like Titanic . I like science fiction. My friend likes technology and we talk about technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/tv-drama-is-recommended/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/tv-drama-is-recommended/</guid>
      <description>Conversation 推荐10部最适合练口语的美剧
我看过超过100部, 超过2000集美剧, 认真练习过超过100集美剧 以下是我认为最适合练口语的10部美剧:
这10部美剧基本都属于情景喜剧中较为生活化的美剧,或者生活剧中较为轻松愉快的美剧
初级篇
Felicity-温馨的大学校园剧, 格调清新, 语速慢, 用词贴近生活, 是最合适初学者的美剧.
Parenthood-温馨的家庭生活剧, 情节感人, 语速适中, 剧情和对白都极其生活化, 真实地道. Desperate Housewives-大名鼎鼎的生活剧, 肥皂剧, 语速适中, 用词上被称为美国中产阶级口语的典范.
中级篇
Friends-经典的情景喜剧, 轻松活泼, 语速适中, Modern Family-情景喜剧新秀, 风趣而温馨, 语速适中, 最大的优势是伪纪录片的形式让对白更加真实口语化.
Raising Hope-描述工薪阶层生活的喜剧, 格调温暖, 语速适中, 最大的优势在于对白中上绝对少有很难的单词.
It&#39;s Always Sunny in Philadelphia-语速超快的情景喜剧, 情节多荒诞和恶搞, 非常贴近美国年轻人说话风格
Brothers and Sisters-温馨感人的家庭剧, 生活剧, 语速适中, 对白精彩. 高级篇
Everwood-感人至极的家庭剧, 语速稍快, 用词极有品味, 难度颇大.
Will and Grace-语速超快的情景喜剧, 对语言的把玩可谓极致, 难度很大.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
2014年12月补充 美剧和其他学习材料相比的劣势:
对于绝大多数想通过美剧来提升英语口语的人来说, 美剧对你太难了. 以前我和我的小伙伴一起读美剧剧本, 做笔记, 把一些精彩的口语表达整理出来; 我们整理了几百个这样的表达, 比如muscle in on the act, catch sb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel cinematic order</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/marvel-cinematic-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/marvel-cinematic-order/</guid>
      <description>转自《漫威系列电影、电视剧的推荐观看顺序是怎样的? - 知乎》
MCU（漫威电影宇宙）补剧建议观影顺序 &amp;amp; MCU 计划电影与TV 本答案只包含MCU！！关于毒液（Sony）、死侍（Fox）、X战警、金刚狼、神奇四侠等电影观看顺序请另寻  非剧情发生时间排序，基本是按照上映时间排序
 钢铁侠（2008） 无敌浩克（2008） 钢铁侠2（2010） [短片 神盾顾问] [短片 寻找雷神锤子路上发生的趣事] 雷神（2011） 美国队长：复仇者先锋（2011） [短片 探员卡特] 复仇者联盟（2012） [短片 47号物品]   钢铁侠3（2013） [短片 王者万岁]神盾局特工 第一季1-7集 雷神2：黑暗世界（2013） 神盾局特工 第一季8-16集 美国队长2：冬日战士（2014） 神盾局特工 第一季17-22集 银河护卫队（2014） 神盾局特工 第二季1-10集特工卡特 第一季神盾局特工 第二季11-19集 复仇者联盟2：奥创纪元（2015） 神盾局特工 第二季20-22集 蚁人（2015） 夜魔侠 第一季 杰西卡-琼斯 第一季   神盾局特工 第三季1-10集 特工卡特 第二季 夜魔侠 第二季 神盾局特工 第三季11-19集 美国队长3：内战（2016） 神盾局特工 第三季20-22集 卢克·凯奇 第一季 神盾局特工 第四季1-6集 奇异博士（2016） 神盾局特工 第四季7-8集 神盾局特工：弹弓 神盾局特工 第四季9-22集 铁拳 第一季 银河护卫队2（2017） 蜘蛛侠：英雄归来（2017） 捍卫者联盟 第一季 异人族 第一季 雷神3：诸神黄昏（2017） 惩罚者 第一季 离家童盟 第一季 黑豹（2018） 杰西卡·琼斯 第二季 神盾局特工 第五季1-18集 复仇者联盟3：无限战争（2018） 神盾局特工 第五季19-22集 卢克凯奇 第二季 斗篷与匕首 第一季 蚁人2：黄蜂女现身（2018） 铁拳 第二季 夜魔侠 第三季 离家童盟 第二季 惩罚者 第二季 惊奇队长（2019） 斗篷与匕首 第二季 复仇者联盟4：终局之战（2019）  神盾局特工 第六季（2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>29 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-29/</guid>
      <description>Conversation I have never been to canada I went to Australia in january exercise go to the gym I pay rent every month for my house she likes to learn languages she wants to be a translator I have never been to canada I went to Australia in january exercise go to the gym I pay rent every month for my house she likes to learn languages she wants to be a translator she wants to learn by herself happy wife , happy life study very hard daily word coca I brush my teeth diary roxanne marie what do you use to brush your teeth I use an electric tooth brush and tooth paste befroe i wash my face I have never been to canada I went to Australia in january exercise go to the gym I pay rent every month for my house she likes to learn languages she wants to be a translator she wants to learn by herself happy wife , happy life study very hard daily word coca I brush my teeth diary roxanne marie what do you use to brush your teeth I use an electric tooth brush and tooth paste befroe i wash my face before past stretch it out stretch every day she does not like swim she like to read!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-28/</guid>
      <description>Conversation You remembered many English words this morning. Yes, it comes from Chinglish but it is used commonly in the United States. Every class has this on the blackboard. I can hear you, I just can&#39;t see you. That usually means that we have a bad connection. yes, every weekend I am learning English and algorithms for work. I prefer to stay home and do BBQ. I think a normal weekend is too short for a trip too because Singapore is a small country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-27/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Ramadan starts on May 6. Buying train tickets online You work 13 hours everyday. the fasting month starts on May 6 You can&#39;t eat or drink during the day The idea of fasting is to think about what it feels like to be poor and not have enough food to eat Muslims can&#39;t eat for the month. Restaurants are open. Because some people have to eat. For example, I can&#39;t fast because I have an illness, and pregnant women can&#39;t fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-24/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m really sorry that I changed the course time. It&#39;s 11:30 PM Singapore time and I just got home. I&#39;m really busy this week. I work every day from 9:30 a.m. to 10:30 p.m. Because my project is an Indonesian project. Next month is a holiday for them, similar to Chinese New Year, your Christmas. We must ensure the stable operation of buying train tickets and plane tickets online. I&#39;m very tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-21/</guid>
      <description>Exercise 1 Vocabulary  immersion [ɪˈmɜːrʒn] Noun
 away of teaching or learning a foreign language which involves only using that language
I took a five-week immersion course in German.   translation [trænsˈleɪʃən] Noun
 words or text that have been changed into another language
She provided an accurate translation of the document. He wrote a translation of the phrases into Russian on the board.   instead [ɪnˈstɛd] Adverb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-20/</guid>
      <description>20 April 2019
 Use English for documents and email. opportunity to work in Singapore You don&#39;t talk to local people much. How long have you been talking on Cambly? Not very long Children&#39;s video like Peppa Pig We can do some lessons to help you develop your vocabulary and pronunciation My father, my mother, my wife and me. She lives with you. They are living in Harbin the male can retire at 65, and the female can retire at 60.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common sentences</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/ommon-sentences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 23:17:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/ommon-sentences/</guid>
      <description> 最近我在学习算法和背单词
 Recently I have been learning algorithms and memorizing words   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx   xxxxxxxxxx
 xxxxxxxxxxxx  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy to Forget Words for Me</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/easy-to-forget-words-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 16:17:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/easy-to-forget-words-for-me/</guid>
      <description>improve opportunity involve reorganize practice emphasize seaweed crunchy establish scene  measure instittion political despite material exactly financial evidence various represent  positive concerned determine indicate demonstrate breath breadth demand survey survive  associate engage encourage academic central century approach invert supreme deny  specific definitely silence appearance appreciate advantage concentrate confidence criticism crisis  preserve perceive presence presentation prospect propose practical controversy vessel considerable  xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx  xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx  xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxx  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>