<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>28 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-28/</guid>
      <description> 28 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I haven&#39;t kept a diary for a long time because I&#39;m looking for new ways to learn English. I&#39;m a software engineer. Why don&#39;t just recite the interview question?   Question 1:
Given a text file of size say 100GB? Task is to find first non repeating word in this file? Constraints: You can traverse the file only once.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-21/</guid>
      <description>21 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was wake up in the morning at eight twenty. I was so tired that I didn&#39;t get up. I opened my eyes as usual to brush my teeth and then went to work. I went to breakfast before I remembered it that I forgot about my phone. So I don&#39;t have time to eat. I bought a loaf of bread and went back home. That is why I was late today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-20/</guid>
      <description>20 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was wake up in the morning at eight o&#39;clock. I opened my eyes as before. I put on my slippers and went to the bathroom brush my teeth. Do these sentences familiar to you? Yes, because I do it every day. Maybe I will do it every day. What did we talk about right now? Oh, I said brush my teeth. Then I go to work at eight forty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-19/</guid>
      <description>19 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was waked up in the morning and open my eyes. I put on my slippers and went to the bathroom to brush my teeth. I feel so hot then I decided to take a bath. Then I put the rice into the lunch box. I’m so amazing because my Wife makes it yesterday. I set off for work at eight fifty. My feet hurt because I fell in the bath last week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>