<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>31 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Conversation politeness because of what matter because of the level of my English. Yes you can say that. It is not impolite. So they want bilingual employees doesn&#39;t give you any salary for two months develop websites or apps What do you want to do I want to call you I am drinking water. I am calling you. you are in the process of doing something I will call you later re: in an email means about re means about or concerning re: your email of May 31, 2019 I got it is past tense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-30/</guid>
      <description> Conversation My wife&#39;s English is better than mine. https://learnenglish.britishcouncil.org/podcasts-professionals/achievement re-dun-dant man-u-fac-tur-ing pre-sent-ing ded-i-ca-tion work-ers ac-knowl-edged loy-al-ty de-cline dis-ap-point-ment pro-mot-ed redundancy - something that is no longer needed ne-go-ti-a-tion dis-cus-sions oc-curs  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-28/</guid>
      <description>Conversation lots of late nights get off work talk with him It&#39;s a different work culture 996 the Korean work culture is very similar to China. A lot of workers have to work overtime with no extra pay. the Japanese have a lot of overtime. stock broker 8 or 9 every night I feel happier than the Japanese engineers. singlish talking with each other word https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Word It&#39;s also written. It is not a slang word that I use because I when I lived in the US that word wasn&#39;t used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-26/</guid>
      <description>Conversation I got up at 11:00. You didn&#39;t go out with your wife. You wanted to rest. You both stayed at home. Maybe I won&#39;t like this. Canada and Australia are slow-paced countries. I can&#39;t adapt to the slow pace. Maybe you can adapt to the pace. Germany. Why Germany? 30 annual holiday Canada is too cold for me. I like Australia. I&#39;m too old to move now. It&#39;s too expensive there Housing is very expensive But housing is expensive 300,000 RMB 60,000 Singapore dollars pounds US dollars, Canadian dollars, Australian dollars 2000=250 dollars Young people leave for work Old people can dance American native English speaker He is a fraud if he is not a native English speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-25/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Very crazy in Jakarta. There is a long history of anti-Chinese feelings in Indonesia. But we have a lot of Chinese-Indonesians living here. Up until about 1998, it was forbidden to teach the chinese language and have Chinese language schools. Because of 1965-1966 there was an attempted coup and the Chinese government was accused of supplying weapons to the rebels. During the Red Guard period of Chinese History. The cultural revolution he helped her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-24/</guid>
      <description>Conversation You published a new version of the website. https://content.cambly.com/2016/07/31/lesson-23-expressing-concern/ annual holiday of 30 days 6 weeks It varies according to companies. vacation might increase after the first year and then maybe every two years after that three or four week vacations but European countries have long vacations. I think France has 30 days In Bali we get a lot of French tourists in August. Most of them come for one month beer lunch under the weather means not well idioms and phrasal verbs don&#39;t make sense most of the time when you are anxious or upset My work is so busy, I feel stressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-19/</guid>
      <description>Conversation shadowing video about business English from the BBC You follow the video Oxford and the immigration policies are better than the US sentence One of the problems with learning a language is that many people try to understand all of the words in a sentence, but you only need to undersand about 70% to understand the meaning https://content.cambly.com/2016/07/31/lesson-21-saying-thank-you/ The best part is what you like about something the best part of work is when it is time to go home thanks a bunch is just a way to say thank you very much bunch is a lot of something thanks a ton is the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-20/</guid>
      <description>Conversation arithmetic vesak day algorithm I have to be able to do it. 5 20 He wants to sell something. Lots of holidays for buying things 8,900 for a sale price We have special sales everyday. Ramadan has sales everyday. they were the first to create the special days. I think that it is the day after Thanksgiving 11/11 Lazada 500 RMB for one cubic meter official You need a lot of money https://content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-18/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Buddhists It is just for Buddhists. The Buddhist religion Tibet She will go to another world tomb sweeping day When Americans die they don&#39;t need money the culture in America is different. People sometimes just go to the cemetary and put flowers on the grave. go to heaven and you can see all of your relatives if they are good people buried cemetery great grandmother is usually not remembered very often great-grandchildren usually don&#39;t know their great-grandmother buried together It is unusual for people to live that long in Indonesia accompany me always ghosts do people in China believe in ghosts so people aren&#39;t afraid of ghosts people are afraid of ghosts in Indonesia garlic around the house to keep the ghosts away a score of 45 45 out of 150 what is it that blesses you science with a lot of hard work and determination I want to try something called shadowing today I read a sentence in the lesson and then you read the same sentence this helps with your pronunciation and intonation https://content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-15/</guid>
      <description>Conversation technical problems with sound student had skype open and it took over his microphone so he couldn&#39;t speak. You saw a movie I saw a movie or I watched a movie A Dog&#39;s Purpose Is it animated? Animated is like a cartoon or like anime crime movie a crying movie because you feel sad a sentimental movie The dog has many lives His master&#39;s leg is hurt split up or broke up In his second life he is a police dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-12/</guid>
      <description>Conversation You went to lift weights. Exercise room I have a big stomach She runs on a treadmill; I life weights. I lift weights. Two times a week when you work. Tuesday and Thursday for forty minutes and three times a week during your holiday. It means Saturday or Sunday. When I leave this country then I might have more free time. Leave the Chinese company. 10-10-7 The Chinese and Japanese 9-5 five days a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-11/</guid>
      <description>Conversation 996 October 15th If you don&#39;t have any errors 5 months You want the most money. How many people are on your team? The team totals 8 people. You have three assistants 2 leaders and six assistants. One team is checking the other team. Every week you publish a new version of the project. You&#39;re looking at the screen everyday. The computer is your partner. Learning, work and play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-10/</guid>
      <description>Conversation borrow money payments[ payments it&#39;s for small purchases there is a limit on how much you can spend Usually you have a day off on Saturday If I have to work, this disorganizes my study plan https://content.cambly.com/2016/05/23/lesson-12-dining-out/ dining out means eating out dining means to eat Let&#39;s dine out tonight at the new restaurant. hot pot cod salmon and tuna are all fish with salmon the l is silent reservation is making a special time to go somewhere and do something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>08 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-08/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Indonesia ramadan you failed because you don&#39;t the function for selecting a seat online. an airplane sear an airplane seat train seat two weeks ago the plane tickets are for your China trip jakarta shopping online app I&#39;ve never heard of that one pintar means smart or clever https://content.cambly.com/2016/05/23/lesson-11-weather-in-sf/ SF stands for San Francisco in California That&#39;s where I used to live Arnold Schwarzenegger is a famous American actor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>05 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-05/</guid>
      <description>Conversation I watched a tech show today Another explanation for the origin of life We study evolution in school The show I&#39;m watching today is another idea that we are aliens （ET） We shouldn&#39;t walk standing up because gravity is too strong It&#39;s very difficult for us to have children Don&#39;t trust science myth I&#39;m trying to figure out what is wrong with my internet. I lost my ethernet connection The Origins of Life Evolution another explanation We are ET.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>06 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-06/</guid>
      <description>Conversation You worked 12 hours. sweat Is it hot and humid in Singapore, or raining. Yesterday and the day before it didn&#39;t rain. Three days ago Yesterday is one day and then you could say the day before yesterday or two days ago, either one June 28th you have annual holiday. From June 28th to July 7th. Your annual holiday is ten days. Five days annual holiday. ten days holiday for 10-20 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>04 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-04/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Yesterday I heard a phrase on a social media app that has two interpretations. The phrase is XXXXX One says: this phrase is not good Another said, this is a phrase that is often used Which one is right Freeze two interpretations of a freeze on social media apps of course Gosling, do you want to move to another country? Yes, of course. it depends on the context of the sentence Do you like being married?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 May 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/05/2019-05-01/</guid>
      <description>Conversation Watching movies from Netflix The Hulk Marvel. Do you like Marvel? I don&#39;t have any time to see all of the movies. You haven&#39;t seen the Avengers: Endgame yet? I like Iron Man. I like happy endings not bad endings. Does your wife like watching the same movies? She likes movies like love movies or romantic movies like Titanic . I like science fiction. My friend likes technology and we talk about technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>