<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 19:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Batch Download YouTuBe Video</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/tools/youtube/batch-install-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 19:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/tools/youtube/batch-install-youtube/</guid>
      <description> youtube-dl github
Install brew install youtube-dl  Download    Expression Description 中文     -i, &amp;ndash;ignore-errors Continue on download errors, for example to skip unavailable videos in a playlist 下载过程中遇到错误继续下载   -r, &amp;ndash;limit-rate RATE Maximum download rate in bytes per second(e.g. 50K or 4.2M) 设置下载速度    youtube-dl -i -r 100K URL  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Song</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:22:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-song/</guid>
      <description>Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids If You&amp;rsquo;re Happy and You Know It - Cool Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Five Little Ducks - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Old MacDonald Had a Farm - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Baa, Baa, Black Sheep - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Ten in a Bed - Fun Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Row Your Boat - Wonderful Lullabies for Children - LooLoo Kids The Wheels On The Bus - Fun Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Itsy Bitsy Spider - Cute Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Sleeping Bunnies - The Cutest Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids One, Two, Buckle My Shoe - Amazing Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Hickory Dickory Dock - Wonderful Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids The Wheels On The Bus - GREAT Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids I&amp;rsquo;m a Little Teapot - Great Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Once I Caught A Fish Alive - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Mary Had a Little Lamb - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Johny Johny Yes Papa - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Rain, Rain Go Away - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Pat-a-Cake - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Humpty Dumpty - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Three Little Kittens - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Miss Polly Had a Dolly - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Baa, Baa, Black Sheep - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Row, Row, Row Your Boat - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Hush, Little Baby - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Incy Wincy Spider - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Head, Shoulders, Knees and Toes - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids The Finger Family - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids If You&amp;rsquo;re Happy And You Know It - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Old MacDonald Had A Farm - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Five Little Monkeys - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids The ABC Song - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids BINGO - THE BEST Song for Children - LooLoo Kids Head, Shoulders, Knees and Toes - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids If You&amp;rsquo;re Happy and You Know It - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star - Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Row Your Boat - Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Bingo - Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Five Little Ducks - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Wheels on the Bus - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids 25 of The Most Awesome Songs for Kids on YouTube The 25 Cutest Songs for Kids on YouTube Five Little Monkeys - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids Old MacDonald Had a Farm - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids The Wheels On The Bus - THE BEST Songs for Children - LooLoo Kids HAPPY BIRTHDAY - Fun Birthday Party Song</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Used</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-used/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 17:10:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-used/</guid>
      <description>demo [&amp;lsquo;deməu] n. 演示；样本唱片；示威；民主党员 valid [&amp;lsquo;vælid] adj. 有效的，有根据的；正当的 equivalent [i&amp;rsquo;kwiv ələ nt] n. 等价物，相等物 adj. 等价的，相等的；同意义的 cause [kɔ:z] n. 原因；事业；目标 vt. 引起；使遭受 single [&amp;lsquo;siŋɡ l] n. 一个；单打；单程票 adj. 单一的；单身的；单程的 vt. 选出 vi. 击出一垒安打 basis [&amp;lsquo;beisis] n. 基础；底部；主要成分；基本原则或原理 deprecate [&amp;lsquo;deprɪke ɪt] vt. 反对；抨击；轻视；声明不赞成 separated [&amp;lsquo;sepəreitid] v. 分开；隔开（ separate的过去式和过去分词） adj. 分开的；分居；不在一起生活的 runtime [rʌn&amp;rsquo;taim] n. 执行时间，运行时间 block [blɔk] n. 块；街区；大厦；障碍物 adj. 成批的，大块的；交通堵塞的 vt. 阻止；阻塞；限制 calling [&amp;lsquo;kɔ:li ŋ] n. 职业；欲望；点名；召集；邀请 v. 召；呼唤（ call的现在分词）；称之为 collection [kə&amp;rsquo;lek ʃən] n.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shine Your Way</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/shine-your-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 16:59:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/shine-your-way/</guid>
      <description>Shine Your Way 荣耀你的路 Owl City;Yuna 【画外音合唱 】 Just before the dawn, When the light&amp;rsquo;s still gone, 就在破晓前，希望仍未现 Shine, shine your way, 让光，荣耀你的路 And you may not know, where to go, 如果你不知，该何去何从 Shine, shine your way 让光，荣耀你的路 【男孩盖 ，唱给全家】 Open road but it&amp;rsquo;s still dark, Build a fire from a spark, 让我们在漆黑之中开拔上路，用心中火把照亮旅途 And shine, shine your way, 因为有光，荣耀你的路 【女孩小伊，唱给全家】 Feed the feeling in your heart, Don&amp;rsquo;t conceal it then you&amp;rsquo;ll start, 旅程定会紧扣心弦， 别再躲藏，也别怕迷途 To find, find your way 去亲近，去追随你的路 【女孩伊，唱给自己】 No one can stop, what has begun, You must believe when I say 谁也不能，阻挠我那驿动的心， 更不能拒绝，我肺腑的诸字诸音 【男孩盖，唱给小伊】 All of your tears will dry faster in the sun, Starting today, Shine, shine, shine, Shine your way 从今后，让阳光，擦干你的泪珠 照着，亮着，荣耀着， 荣耀你的路 【爸爸呆瓜，唱给全家】 There&amp;rsquo;s an open sky, And a reason why, You shine, shine your way, 头顶无边天幕， 理由无需解读， 就让你自己，荣耀你的路 【妈妈，唱给爸爸】 There&amp;rsquo;s so much to learn, And now it&amp;rsquo;s your turn, To shine, shine your way 你学会化解无数， 你已经踏上坦途， 就让你自己，荣耀你的路 【画外音】 There&amp;rsquo;s a feeling deep inside, You can let it be your guide, 你紧随内心深处， 你不断兑现航图， To find, find your way, 去亲近，去拥抱你的路 【爸爸呆瓜与男孩盖，唱给全家】 And there&amp;rsquo;s no time for us to waste, Got to take a leap of faith, And fly, fly away 让我们再也无需，分秒踌躇， 让我们纵身一跃，直达终途， 让我们展翅飞翔，远离迷雾 Don&amp;rsquo;t have to walk, Now you can run, Nothing can get in your way 别再犹豫踌躇， 你只要飞奔加速， 让我们路上，心无旁鹜 All of your tears will dry faster in the sun, Starting today, Shine, shine, shine, Shine your way 从今后，让阳光，擦干你的泪珠 就让光，照着，亮着 荣耀着你的路 【全家合唱】 Morning is breaking, Darkness is fading, We found a way to the light, It&amp;rsquo;s such a beautiful sight 黎明它正在来路， 黑暗它自然退出， 我们已经，踏上坦途， 奇美妙景，历历在目 【爸爸呆瓜，唱给全家】 Any time, anywhere, Turn around and I&amp;rsquo;ll be there, To shine, shine your way 无论何时，你身在何处， 只要暮然回首，我必然在那， 在照耀着，荣耀你的路 Like a star burning bright, Lighting up the darkest night, I&amp;rsquo;ll shine, shine your way 我誓化作燃烧的恒星， 去点亮无尽黑暗的眼睛， 让我照亮，指引你的前行 【全家感恩唱给爸爸】 Now I can see, You are the one, Sent here to show me the way 我心如明镜，你代表那个神灵， 派遣此地，为我揭示谜底 All of your tears will dry faster in the sun, Starting today, Shine, shine, shine, 从今后，让阳光，擦干你的泪珠 照着，亮着，荣耀着， 荣耀你的路 【全家合唱，骄傲地唱给全世界】 We&amp;rsquo;re on our way, Shine, shine, shine, 我们已经上路， 照着，亮着，荣耀着 That&amp;rsquo;s what we say, Shine, shine, shine, 我们大声欢歌， 照着，亮着，荣耀着 Shine your way 荣耀你的路 There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why You shine, shine your way 理由无需解读， 就让你自己，荣耀你的路 All of our tears will dry faster in the sun Shine your way 你的所有泪珠，会向阳光认输， 让一切，荣耀着你的路</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Month</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 17:55:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-month/</guid>
      <description>January -&amp;gt; Jan.
February -&amp;gt; Feb.
March -&amp;gt; Mar.
April -&amp;gt; Apr.
May -&amp;gt; May.
June -&amp;gt; Jun.
July -&amp;gt; Jul.
August -&amp;gt; Aug.
September -&amp;gt; Sept.
October -&amp;gt; Oct.
November -&amp;gt; Nov.
December -&amp;gt; Dec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Ordinal Numeral</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-ordinal-numeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 16:55:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-ordinal-numeral/</guid>
      <description>第1 first
第2 second
第3 third
第4 fourth
第5 fifth
第6 sixth
第7 seventh
第8 eighth
第9 ninth
第10 tenth
第11 eleventh
第12 twelfth
第13 thirteenth
第14 fourteenth
第15 fifteenth
第16 sixteenth
第17 seventeenth
第18 eighteenth
第19 nineteenth
第20 twentieth
第21 twenty-first
第22 twenty-second
第23 twenty-third
第24 twenty-fourth
第25 twenty-fifth
第26 twenty-sixth
第27 twenty-seventh
第28 twenty-eighth
第29 twenty-ninth
第30 thirtieth
第31 thirty-first
第32 thirty-second
第33 thirty-third
第34 thirty-fourth
第35 thirty-fifth</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Technology</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 17:28:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-technology/</guid>
      <description>ELK（ElasticSearch, Logstash, Kibana） ElasticSearch [ɪ&amp;rsquo;læstɪk]
Logstash [stæʃ] Kibana
consumer Producer broker partition [pɑː&amp;rsquo;tɪʃ(ə)n] 分区 cluster [&amp;lsquo;klʌstə] 集群 distributed [dɪ&amp;rsquo;strɪbjʊtɪd] 分布式的 partitioned [pɑr&amp;rsquo;tɪʃən] 分区的；分段的</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Joke</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 17:00:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/english-joke/</guid>
      <description>英语短篇笑话70篇 The Perfect Son. A: I have the perfect son. B: Does he smoke? A: No, he doesn’t. B: Does he drink whiskey? A: No, he doesn’t. B: Does he ever come home late? A: No, he doesn’t. B: I guess you really do have the perfect son. How old is he? A: He will be six months old next Wednesday. Girl: You would be a good dancer except for two things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scjp Word</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/scjp-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 14:37:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2017/scjp-word/</guid>
      <description>demo [&amp;lsquo;deməu]  n. 演示；样本唱片；示威；民主党员  comma [&amp;lsquo;kɔmə]  n. 逗号；停顿  cause [kɔ:z]  n. 原因；事业；目标 vt. 引起；使遭受  illegal [i&amp;rsquo;li:gəl]  n. 非法移民；间谍 adj. [法] 非法的；违法的；违反规则的  separated [&amp;lsquo;sepəreitid]  v. 分开；隔开（separate的过去式和过去分词） adj. 分开的；分居；不在一起生活的  collection [kə&amp;rsquo;lekʃən]  n. 采集，聚集；[税收] 征收；收藏品；募捐  garbage [&amp;lsquo;gɑːbɪdʒ]  n. 垃圾；废物  eligible [&amp;lsquo;elidʒəbl]  n. 合格者；适任者；有资格者 adj. 合格的，合适的；符合条件的；有资格当选的  dot [dɔt]  n. 点，圆点；嫁妆 vt. 加小点于 vi. 打上点  statement [&amp;lsquo;steitmənt]  n.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>