<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Forwarded on Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/forwarded/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Forwarded on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:13:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/forwarded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Go</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:13:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-awesome/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Platforms Programming Languages Front-End Development Back-End Development Computer Science Big Data Theory Books Editors Gaming Development Environment Entertainment Databases Media Learn Security Content Management Systems Hardware Business Work Networking Decentralized Systems Miscellaneous Related  Platforms  Node.js - Async non-blocking event-driven JavaScript runtime built on Chrome&amp;rsquo;s V8 JavaScript engine.  Cross-Platform - Writing cross-platform code on Node.js.  Frontend Development iOS - Mobile operating system for Apple phones and tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang Game Project</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-game-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:13:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-game-project/</guid>
      <description>Games on GitHub  Below is a list of open source games and game-related projects that can be found on GitHub - old school text adventures, educational games, 8-bit platform games, browser-based games, indie games, GameJam projects, add-ons/maps/hacks/plugins for commercial games, libraries, frameworks, engines, you name it.
Contributing If you&amp;rsquo;d like to add a repository to the list, please create an Issue, or fork this repository and submit a pull request (click here to edit this file from github).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang Knowledge</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:13:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/golang-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Golang知识图谱 Golang知识图谱</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>