<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diary on Sillyhat Blog</title>
    <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diary on Sillyhat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sillyhatxu.com/tags/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel cinematic order</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/marvel-cinematic-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/marvel-cinematic-order/</guid>
      <description>转自《漫威系列电影、电视剧的推荐观看顺序是怎样的? - 知乎》
MCU（漫威电影宇宙）补剧建议观影顺序 &amp;amp; MCU 计划电影与TV 本答案只包含MCU！！关于毒液（Sony）、死侍（Fox）、X战警、金刚狼、神奇四侠等电影观看顺序请另寻  非剧情发生时间排序，基本是按照上映时间排序
 钢铁侠（2008） 无敌浩克（2008） 钢铁侠2（2010） [短片 神盾顾问] [短片 寻找雷神锤子路上发生的趣事] 雷神（2011） 美国队长：复仇者先锋（2011） [短片 探员卡特] 复仇者联盟（2012） [短片 47号物品]   钢铁侠3（2013） [短片 王者万岁]神盾局特工 第一季1-7集 雷神2：黑暗世界（2013） 神盾局特工 第一季8-16集 美国队长2：冬日战士（2014） 神盾局特工 第一季17-22集 银河护卫队（2014） 神盾局特工 第二季1-10集特工卡特 第一季神盾局特工 第二季11-19集 复仇者联盟2：奥创纪元（2015） 神盾局特工 第二季20-22集 蚁人（2015） 夜魔侠 第一季 杰西卡-琼斯 第一季   神盾局特工 第三季1-10集 特工卡特 第二季 夜魔侠 第二季 神盾局特工 第三季11-19集 美国队长3：内战（2016） 神盾局特工 第三季20-22集 卢克·凯奇 第一季 神盾局特工 第四季1-6集 奇异博士（2016） 神盾局特工 第四季7-8集 神盾局特工：弹弓 神盾局特工 第四季9-22集 铁拳 第一季 银河护卫队2（2017） 蜘蛛侠：英雄归来（2017） 捍卫者联盟 第一季 异人族 第一季 雷神3：诸神黄昏（2017） 惩罚者 第一季 离家童盟 第一季 黑豹（2018） 杰西卡·琼斯 第二季 神盾局特工 第五季1-18集 复仇者联盟3：无限战争（2018） 神盾局特工 第五季19-22集 卢克凯奇 第二季 斗篷与匕首 第一季 蚁人2：黄蜂女现身（2018） 铁拳 第二季 夜魔侠 第三季 离家童盟 第二季 惩罚者 第二季 惊奇队长（2019） 斗篷与匕首 第二季 复仇者联盟4：终局之战（2019）  神盾局特工 第六季（2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-24/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m really sorry that I changed the course time. It&#39;s 11:30 PM Singapore time and I just got home. I&#39;m really busy this week. I work every day from 9:30 a.m. to 10:30 p.m. Because my project is an Indonesian project. Next month is a holiday for them, similar to Chinese New Year, your Christmas. We must ensure the stable operation of buying train tickets and plane tickets online. I&#39;m very tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 April 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/04/2019-04-20/</guid>
      <description>20 April 2019
 Use English for documents and email. opportunity to work in Singapore You don&#39;t talk to local people much. How long have you been talking on Cambly? Not very long Children&#39;s video like Peppa Pig We can do some lessons to help you develop your vocabulary and pronunciation My father, my mother, my wife and me. She lives with you. They are living in Harbin the male can retire at 65, and the female can retire at 60.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a killer software engineering resume</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/writing-a-killer-software-engineering-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 23:13:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/forwarded/2019/writing-a-killer-software-engineering-resume/</guid>
      <description>An in-depth analysis of the résumé that got me interviews at Google, Facebook, Amazon, Microsoft, Apple, and more.
 这是一篇简历深度分析，它让我得到了 Google，Facebook，Amazon，Microsoft，Apple 等众多公司的面试机会。
 This résumé got me interviews at Google, Facebook, Amazon, Microsoft, and Apple.
 这篇简历让我进入了 Google，Facebook，Amazon，Microsoft 和 Apple 的面试环节。
 I obtained these interviews by sending my résumé to the résumé black hole, also known as applying online.
 我通过把我的简历持续不断的投入简历黑洞，也就是大家熟悉的网上申请，来获得了这些面试机会。
 Applying online is the most common way people go about applying for a job and therefore the least effective way to land an interview due to competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-28/</guid>
      <description> 28 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I haven&#39;t kept a diary for a long time because I&#39;m looking for new ways to learn English. I&#39;m a software engineer. Why don&#39;t just recite the interview question?   Question 1:
Given a text file of size say 100GB? Task is to find first non repeating word in this file? Constraints: You can traverse the file only once.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-21/</guid>
      <description>21 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was wake up in the morning at eight twenty. I was so tired that I didn&#39;t get up. I opened my eyes as usual to brush my teeth and then went to work. I went to breakfast before I remembered it that I forgot about my phone. So I don&#39;t have time to eat. I bought a loaf of bread and went back home. That is why I was late today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-20/</guid>
      <description>20 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was wake up in the morning at eight o&#39;clock. I opened my eyes as before. I put on my slippers and went to the bathroom brush my teeth. Do these sentences familiar to you? Yes, because I do it every day. Maybe I will do it every day. What did we talk about right now? Oh, I said brush my teeth. Then I go to work at eight forty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19 March 2019</title>
      <link>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sillyhatxu.com/english/2019/03/2019-03-19/</guid>
      <description>19 Mar,2019 Tuesday
 I was waked up in the morning and open my eyes. I put on my slippers and went to the bathroom to brush my teeth. I feel so hot then I decided to take a bath. Then I put the rice into the lunch box. I’m so amazing because my Wife makes it yesterday. I set off for work at eight fifty. My feet hurt because I fell in the bath last week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>